<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="amethyst">
        Amethyst( Kateala), Code: ASP 15 (FOR ANY QUERY ON AMETHYST CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Amethyst is a beautiful Gemstone which is Violet-Purple in colour. It has an excellent lustre and transparency.It is traditionally considered, a great help, in getting rid of intoxication. It is even said that if you drink wine in a cup made of Amethyst, it will loose its intoxicating effect. This stone is believed to heal females suffering from gynecological problems. I have been using this Gem for its healing properties since many years. When I did courses in Pranic Healing in 1998 the Healing powers of this Gemstone became more clear to me and I have discovered that its rays can transform the depressed minds and all kinds of mental problems can be healed by this Gemstone. The people who get agitated fast can be relieved of their behavioral problems by the use of this Gem.
\n\n
Amethyst can be used by people involved in occult sciences, as it is said to have strong spiritual powers. The Greeks believed that use of this Gem gave un-ending love and affection. Amethyst is a BIRTHSTONE of people born in February but others may also wear it. This gem is useful in controlling one\'s tendency of getting distracted, switching so often from one activity to the other. Since it brings about financial stability, it is of great help to those who find it difficult to manage their financial affairs.
\n\n
This Gemstone is a great help to people with broken hearts and those suffering from loneliness. Nine Gems of Amethyst, with a strong Aura, if worn in a bracket can protect the wearer from Evil Eye.
\n\n
visit <b>www.astropankaj.com</b> to find out:
\n\t
Who should wear an Amethyst?\n\t
Benefits of Wearing an Amethyst?\n\t
Mantra for Amethyst\n\t
How to wear an Amethyst\n\t
Finger for Amethyst\n\t
When to wear an Amethyst?\n\t

\n\n
Amethyst Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.\n
Weight Available 3.25 Rt. to 21.25 Rt.
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Mineral variety\n\t
Crystal system : rhombohedral class 32\n\t
Crystal habit : 6-sided prism ending in 6-sided pyramid (typical)\n\t
Color : Colorless, Purple, violet\n\t
Chemical formula : Silica (silicon dioxide, SiO2)\n\t
Twinning : Dauphine law, Brazil law, and Japan law\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7–lower in impure varieties\n\t
Luster : Vitreous/glossy\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent to translucent\n\t
Optical properties : Uniaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.543–1.553, 1.552–1.554\n\t
Solubility : insoluble in common solvents\n\t
Melting point : 1650±75 °C\n\t
Fracture : Conchoidal\n\t
Cleavage : None
</b>

    </string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">212370842842907</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb212370842842907</string>


    <string name="amethyst2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
</string>

    <string name="aquamarine">
Aquamarine( Beruj), Code: ASP 05 (FOR ANY QUERY ON AQUAMARINE CALL 0091 - 9213932017) The most valuable colour of Aquamarine is a rich, sky blue. The lustre is vitreous and not exceptional. The most common art of aquamarine is the emerald type. It is also available in oval or pear shaped. The green of Aquamarine is a watery green without any trace of yellow and is due to iron, not chromium, as can be seen from examination with a gemmological stethoscope. It also has a grey or violet tinge. Rich blue stone several carats in weight are among the most valuable of secondary gems pale or green stones are less valuable than rich blue stones. Benefits: Said to enhance one\'s attractiveness in the eyes of the opposite sex. The gem increases beauty and calmness and it is widely used by astrologers worldwide. It is said to bring love and understanding. Who Should Wear It? A beautiful gem which is most useful for those born under the Zodiac Sign Pisces. It also controls flaring of temper and regulating ego problems. It is highly recommended for those involved in humanitarian causes. Quality : Premium
\n<b>Aquamarine Rs. 2100 Per Ratti.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="aquamarine2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 6825.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 8925.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 11025.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 13125.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 15225.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 17325.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 19425.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 21525 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 23625.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 25725.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 27825.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 29925.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 32025.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 34125.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 36225.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 38325.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 40425.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 42525.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 44625.00 INR
</string>

    <string name="blackonyx1">
Black Onyx Cabochon, (FOR ANY QUERY ON Black Onyx Cabochon CALL 0091 - 9213932017) A Gem, which is beautiful and full of mystic widely used by people who are trying to awaken their Kundalini Power, this gemstone gives a star effect when seen under a single source of light. Benefits: Known to take away the malefic effects of Rahu (Dragon\'s Head) and Ketu (Dragon\'s Tail), his gemstone is widely used to ward off the evil eye. It takes out the negative energy of the chakra on which it is worn and thus improves the physical and mental health of the person. Who should wear it? This gem is very useful for the serious minded people who believe in hard work. This helps to take failures as stepping stones to success and rise in life despite all the factors working against one\'s success. The Black Onyx Cabochon is known to develop great business leads and management experts. Quality : Premium
\n\n
Black Onyx Cabochon <b>Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Oxide mineral\n\t
Chemical formula : Silica (silicon dioxide, SiO2)\n\t
Molar mass : 60 g / mol\n\t
Color : Various\n\t
Crystal system : Trigonal, Monoclinic\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 6–7\n\t
Luster : Vitreous, silky\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.65 – 2.667\n\t
Diaphaneity : Translucent\n\t
Hardness (Mohs scale) : 7
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="blackonyx2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 357.50.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 467.50 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 577.50 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 687.50 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 797.50 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 907.50 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1017.50 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1127.50 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.50 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 1347.50 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 1457.50 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 1567.50 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 1677.50 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 1787.50 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 1897.50 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 2007.50 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 2117.50 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 2227.50 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 2337.50 INR
</string>

    <string name="blackrainbow">
        <b>Black Rainbow Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="blackrainbow1">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 357.50.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 467.50 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 577.50 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 687.50 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 797.50 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 907.50 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1017.50 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1127.50 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.50 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 1347.50 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 1457.50 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 1567.50 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 1677.50 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 1787.50 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 1897.50 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 2007.50 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 2117.50 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 2227.50 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 2337.50 INR
</string>

    <string name="blackstar">
Black Star, Code: ASP 17 (FOR ANY QUERY ON BLACK STAR CALL 0091 - 9213932017) A Gem, which is beautiful and full of mystic widely used by people who are trying to awaken their Kundalini Power, this gemstone gives a star effect when seen under a single source of light. Benefits: Known to take away the malefic effects of Rahu (Dragon\'s Head) and Ketu (Dragon\'s Tail), his gemstone is widely used to ward off the evil eye. It takes out the negative energy of the chakra on which it is worn and thus improves the physical and mental health of the person. Who should wear it? This gem is very useful for the serious minded people who believe in hard work. This helps to take failures as stepping stones to success and rise in life despite all the factors working against one\'s success. The Black star is known to develop great business leads and management experts. Quality : Premium
\n\n
<b>Black Star Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.
</b>
        \n\n\t
<b>
Category : Oxide mineral\n\t
Chemical formula : Silica (silicon dioxide, SiO2)\n\t
Molar mass : 60 g / mol\n\t
Color : Various\n\t
Crystal system : Trigonal, Monoclinic\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 6–7\n\t
Luster : Vitreous, silky\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.65 – 2.667\n\t
Diaphaneity : Translucent\n\t
Hardness (Mohs scale) : 7
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="blackstar1">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
</string>

    <string name="bluetopaz">
BlueTopaz: Blue in colour, this transparent and hard stone takes a high polish and makes a spectacular jewellery stone. Blue Topaz has uniform sky blue colour. Its colour is mostly pale but sometimes it is also intense blue in colour. Occasionally, coming with a grey or a greenish tinge, the Blue Topaz is mostly free of inclusions. Oval is the most common cut but mixed cut, step cut etc. are also used. Benefits: It is a gem that induces sleep and rest. It keeps the temper cool and makes one generous and kind hearted. It improves the financial assets and gives financial stability. This gem enhances sincerity in all relations of life. Quality : Premium
\n\n<b>Blue Topaz Rs. 550.00 Per Ratti, 1100.00 Per Ratti, 2100.00 Per Ratti.
</b>
        \n\n\t
<b>
Category : Mineral\n\t
Crystal system : Orthorhombic\n\t
Chemical formula : (Mg, Fe)2SiO4\n\t
Color : Yellow, to yellow-green, olive-green, to brownish, sometimes a lime-green, to emerald-ish hue\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 6.5–7\n\t
Luster : Vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.2–4.3\n\t
Refractive index : 1.64–1.70
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bluetopaz1">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
       \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 1787.50 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 2337.50 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 2887.50 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 3437.50 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 3987.50 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 4537.50 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 5087.50 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 5637.50 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 6137.50 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 6737.50 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 7287.50 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 7837.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 8387.50 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 8937.50 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 9437.50 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 10037.50 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 10587.50 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 11137.50 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 11687.50 INR
</string>

    <string name="beruj">
Beruj ( Aquamarine), (FOR ANY QUERY ON BERUJ CALL 0091 - 9213932017) The most valuable colour of Beruj is a rich, sky blue. The lustre is vitreous and not exceptional. The most common art of Beruj is the emerald type. It is also available in oval or pear shaped. The green of Beruj is a watery green without any trace of yellow and is due to iron, not chromium, as can be seen from examination with a gemmological stethoscope. It also has a grey or violet tinge. Rich blue stone several carats in weight are among the most valuable of secondary gems pale or green stones are less valuable than rich blue stones. Benefits: Said to enhance one\'s attractiveness in the eyes of the opposite sex. The gem increases beauty and calmness and it is widely used by astrologers worldwide. It is said to bring love and understanding. Who Should Wear It? A beautiful gem which is most useful for those born under the Zodiac Sign Pisces. It also controls flaring of temper and regulating ego problems. It is highly recommended for those involved in humanitarian causes. Quality : Premium
        \n\n
<b>Aquamarine Rs. 550 Per Ratti.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="beruj2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 1787.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 2337.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 2887.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 13125.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 15225.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 17325.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 19425.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 21525 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 23625.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 25725.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 27825.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 29925.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 32025.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 34125.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 36225.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 38325.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 40425.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 42525.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 44625.00 INR
</string>

    <string name="citrine">
Citrine Ideally suited for people born in Zodiac signs ruled by Jupiter i.e., Sagittarius and Pisces, the Citrine is also recommended as a lucky gem of Scorpio and Aries. Benefits: An effective gem, which almost acts as a mental tonic, the Citrine confers dignity and nobility of character. One gets innovative ideas by wearing this gem, and learns to control anger and also turning one\'s energies positively. Who should wear it? Ideally suited for people born in Zodiac signs ruled by Jupiter i.e., Sagittarius and Pisces, the Golden Topaz is also recommended as a lucky gem of Scorpio and Aries. Quality : Premium
\n\n\t
<b>Citrine Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Silicate mineral\n\t
Crystal symmetry : Orthorhombic dipyramidal\n\t
Chemical formula : Al2SiO4(F,OH)2\n\t
Strunz classification : 9.AF.35\n\t
Color : Colorless, blue, brown, orange, gray, yellow, green, pink and reddish pink\n\t
Crystal system : Orthorhombic\n\t
Crystal habit : Prismatic crystals with faces striated parallel to long dimension; also columnar, compact, massive\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 8 (defining mineral)\n\t
Luster : Vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.606–1.629, 1.609–1.631, 1.616–1.638
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="citrine2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
</string>

    <string name="chandramani">
Chandramani, Chandramani generally has an almost transparent ground, which is practically colorless, pale grey or tinged with yellow, with a whitish to silvery white or blue shimmer. It is normally cut into curved pieces for threading into necklaces etc. It is also cut as high-domed cabochons and the sheen is concentrated at the top in a bright spot that sometimes extends across the stone as a distinct \'eye\'. Some Chandramani may have a second ray at right angles to first, forming a cross. Benefits: This is a highly beneficial gem that can be used with great results by all who want to keep their cool and be less affected by the changes in their surroundings said to relieve one of insomnia and low fever. This helps in controlling tempers or excitement. This also gives better concentration of mind and helps in marital problems. In Medical Astrology this helps those suffering from heart ailments, gynecological problems, epilepsy, mental ailments etc. Who should wear it: Considered to be gem of Moon it is best suited for people born under the zodiac sign Cancer. It is said to keep their erratic temperament under control.
\n\n
<b>Chandramani Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Feldspar variety\n\t
Color : Can be numerous colors, including blue, grey, white, pink, green and brown\n\t
Fracture : uneven to conchoidal\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 6.0\n\t
Luster : Opalescent\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.61
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="chandramani2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n
        \t3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
</string>

    <string name="dhunela">
        Dhunela, Code: ASP 21(Smoky Topaz)
\n\n
A brilliant Gem of smoky colour used extensively to ward off evil spirits, Smoky Topaz is especially useful for people facing unfulfilled love. Besides giving one success in love, it is said to protect the wearer from depressions and sleeplessness. Benefits: It has great spiritual, medicinal and super natural power that holds the faith of many and is of immense use to people interested in occult. Also useful in healing eye infections, eye sores, stomach ailments, stomach ulcers, throat infections, giddiness and blood poisoning. Who should wear it? This is a highly recommended colour for research scholars and those who want to acquire a flair for creativity. Quality : Premiu
\n\n<b>Dhunela Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti. </b>
    </string>
    <string name="dhunela2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="feroja">
        Feroza is one of the few Gems outside the "Nine Precious Gems" that has a huge demand both for Astrological purposes and in Jewellery.
\n\n
A gemstone with soft hue - pleasing to eyes and pocket friendly. It is recommended to people facing bouts of high temper causing them much damage in life. This stone is especially recommended to people that face reversals in love again and again. The Gemstone for Venus and recommended to people born in Taurus and Libra ascendants
\n\n
I have been recommending Feroza to people suffering from heart aces, problems in love affairs, depressions etc. This Gemstone being related to Venus also improves creativity and Krishma of the wearer.
\n\n
In Jewellery it is used in making strings and cabochons that are then set in silver and gold Jewellery. The traditional Rajasthani Jewellery had small gemstone of Feroza, Moonga, Moti, Panna, Manik and Hira Polki.
\n\n
In troubled marriages this is a golden remedy. If husband - wife have compatibility problems then wearing a Feroza by both of them can greatly change the scene.
\n\n
My Guruji considered it a spiritual stone and kept his right hand on a big piece of this Gemstone while meditating. One of his pupils who was very active faced huge problems in entering the meditative trance - now this was very necessary for the education he was imparting to us so he suggested that he should hold the big Feroza Stone all day in his hand. After this he was able to meditate in 5 days. Such are the unique powers possessed by this gemstone.
\n\n
One well known actor named Salman Khan wears this Feroza Gemstone in a chain like silver bracelet. Due to this it is becoming very popular with young Indian males.

\n\n
Who should wear a Feroza.
\n\t
1. Those having love affairs must wear this Gemstone.\n\t
2. People who get stressed very quickly can benefit from this Gemstone.\n\t
3. If a person wants to reach high levels in Spiritual life then this Gemstone is beneficial to him.\n\n\t
4. Cinema artists and aspiring artists gain a lot of confidence by wearing a good Feroza

\n\n
Benefits of Wearing an Feroza.
\n\t
1. Gives peace of mind.\n\t
2. Improves creativity.\n\t
3. Improves attractiveness.\n\t
4. A good Feroza Gemstone if worn in a pendant can give man an unfair advantage in dealing with females.\n\n\t
5. Chronic head aces can be cured by regular use of a good Feroza Stone

\n\n
        visit <b>www.astropankaj.com to know:</b>\n\t
Mantra for Feroza.\n\t
How to wear an Feroza?\n\t
Finger for Feroza.\n\t
When to wear an Feroza?

\n\n
<b>Feroza Rs. 350.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Phosphate minerals\n\t
Chemical formula : CuAl6(PO4)4(OH)8·4H2O\n\t
Strunz classification : 08.DD.15\n\t
Color : Blue, blue-green, green\n\t
Crystal system : Triclinic\n\t
Crystal habit : Massive, nodular\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 5-7\n\t
Luster : Waxy to subvitreous\n\t
Streak : Bluish white\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.6-2.9\n\t
Pleochroism : Weak\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.610, 1.615, 1.650
</b>

    </string>
    <string name="feroja2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 1137.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 1487.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 1837.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 2187.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 2537.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 2887.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 3237.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 3587.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 3937.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 4287.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 4637.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4987.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 5337.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 5687.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 6037.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 6387.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 6737.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 7087.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 7437.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="garnet">
        Garnet (Tamadaa), The Colour of garnet is mostly reddish brown buts it can be red, light red, violet, purple etc. Garnets are usually semi-opaque but can be transparent and limpid with highly lustrous faces. They have no cleavage and can be made into Cabochons or faceted with an oval or mixed cut. Widely used in Jewellery and as strings, Garnet is also the birthstone for people born in January. Benefits: antidote for snake bites and for food poisoning. The use of this gem ensures long, fruitful and un-interrupted professional life. This helps in prosperity by facilitating gradual accumulation of wealth. Who should wear it? It is good for people having birth numbers 4 or 8. It is very useful for females having delicate health or suffering from body pains, headaches etc. Quality : Premium
\n\n
<b>Garnet Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Nesosilicate\n\t
Chemical formula : The general formula X3Y2(SiO4)3\n\t
Crystal habit : Rhombic dodecahedra or cubic\n\t
Fracture : conchoidal to uneven\n\t
Crystal system : \n\t\tCubic rhombic dodecahedron,\n\t\ticositetrahedron\n\t
Cleavage : Indistinct\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 6.5 - 7.5\n\t
Luster : vitreous to resinous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.1 - 4.3\n\t
Birefringence : None\n\t
Pleochroism : None\n\t
Refractive index : 1.72 - 1.94
</b>

    </string>
    <string name="garnet2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="goldentopaz">
        Golden Topaz( Citrine ), Code: ASP 16 ( SUNEHLA ) (FOR ANY QUERY ON GOLDEN TOPAZ CALL 0091 - 9213932017)Ideally suited for people born in Zodiac signs ruled by Jupiter i.e., Sagittarius and Pisces, the Golden Topaz is also recommended as a lucky gem of Scorpio and Aries. Benefits: An effective gem, which almost acts as a mental tonic, the Golden Topaz confers dignity and nobility of character. One gets innovative ideas by wearing this gem, and learns to control anger and also turning one\'s energies positively. Who should wear it? Ideally suited for people born in Zodiac signs ruled by Jupiter i.e., Sagittarius and Pisces, the Golden Topaz is also recommended as a lucky gem of Scorpio and Aries. Quality : Premium
<b>\n\n
Golden Topaz Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti. </b>
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Silicate mineral\n\t
Crystal symmetry : Orthorhombic dipyramidal\n\t
Chemical formula : Al2SiO4(F,OH)2\n\t
Strunz classification : 9.AF.35\n\t
Color : Colorless, blue, brown, orange, gray, yellow, green, pink and reddish pink\n\t
Crystal system : Orthorhombic\n\t
Crystal habit : Prismatic crystals with faces striated parallel to long dimension; also columnar, compact, massive\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 8 (defining mineral)\n\t
Luster : Vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.606–1.629, 1.609–1.631, 1.616–1.638
</b>
    </string>

    <string name="greenamethyst">
        Green Amethyst is one gemstone with an excellent lustre and transparency. Found in a number of cuts like oval, drop mixed cuts, step cuts, the distribution of colour in striking patches, and bands is characteristic. In case of Green Amethyst, when you see it with a lens, you will see inclusions and a series of discontinuous wavy parallel lines. Benefits: It is traditionally considered, a great help, in getting rid of intoxication. It is even said that if you drink wine in a cup made of Green Amethyst, it will loose its intoxicating effect. This stone is believed to heal females suffering from gynecological problems. Also widely used by people involved in occult sciences, as it is said to have impart strong spiritual powers. Who should wear it? The Greeks believed that use of this gem gave un-ending love and affection. Green Amethyst is a birthstone of people born in February but others may also wear it. This gem is useful in controlling one\'s tendency of getting distracted, switching so often from one activity to the other. Since it brings about financial stability, it is of great help to those who find it difficult to manage their financial affairs.
\n\n
<b>Green Amethyst Rs. 250.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
<b>Category : Mineral variety\n\t
Crystal system : rhombohedral class 32\n\t
Crystal habit : 6-sided prism ending in 6-sided pyramid (typical)\n\t
Color : Colorless, Purple, violet\n\t
Chemical formula : Silica (silicon dioxide, SiO2)\n\t
Twinning : Dauphine law, Brazil law, and Japan law\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7–lower in impure varieties\n\t
Luster : Vitreous/glossy\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent to translucent\n\t
Optical properties : Uniaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.543–1.553, 1.552–1.554\n\t
Solubility : insoluble in common solvents\n\t
Melting point : 1650±75 °C\n\t
Fracture : Conchoidal\n\t
Cleavage : None</b>
    </string>
    <string name="greenamethyst2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 812.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 1062.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 1312.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 1562.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1812.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 2062.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 2312.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 2562.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 2812.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3062.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3312.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 352.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 3812.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4062.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 4312.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 4562.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 4812.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 10125.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 10625.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="greenfluorite">
        Green Florite is a very beautiful Gemstone. Green in colour it is an excellent substitute of Emerald and a Gem Stone of planet Mercury and Ganesha. It is said to bring wealth and serinity. It calms the nervous system, reduces the anxiety and improves the communicaation skills of the wearer. Green Florite can improve the confidence level of the person also.
\n\n
<b>Green Florite Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
<b>\n\n\t
Category : Halide mineral\n\t
Crystal system : Isometric, cF12, SpaceGroup Fm3m, No. 225\n\t
Crystal habit : Occurs as well-formed coarse sized crystals also nodular, botryoidal, rarely columnar or fibrous; granular, massive\n\n\t
Color : Colorless, white, purple, blue, green, yellow, orange, red, pink, brown, bluish black; commonly zoned\n\n\t
Chemical formula : CaF2\n\t
Twinning : Common on {111}, interpenetrant, flattened\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 4 (defining mineral)\n\t
Luster : Vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.175–3.184; to 3.56 if high in rare-earth elements\n\n\t
Strunz classification : 03.AB.25\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent to translucent\n\t
Optical properties : Isotropic; weak anomalous anisotropism\n\t
Refractive index : 1.433–1.448
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="greenfluorite2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="greengarnet">
        The Colour of green garnet is mostly green and reddish brown buts it can be red, green, light red, violet, purple etc. Green Garnets are usually semi-opaque but can be transparent and limpid with highly lustrous faces. They have no cleavage and can be made into Cabochons or faceted with an oval or mixed cut. Widely used in Jewellery and as strings, Green Garnet is also the birthstone for people born in January. Benefits: antidote for snake bites and for food poisoning. The use of this gem ensures long, fruitful and un-interrupted professional life. This helps in prosperity by facilitating gradual accumulation of wealth. Who should wear it? It is good for people having birth numbers 4 or 8. It is very useful for females having delicate health or suffering from body pains, headaches etc. Quality : Premium
\n\n
<b>Green Garnet | Vasonite Rs. 550.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
Category : Nesosilicate\n\t
Crystal System : Cubic rhombic dodecahedron,icositetrahedron\n\t
Chemical formula : The general formula X3Y2(SiO4)3\n\t
Crystal habit : Rhombic dodecahedra or cubic\n\t
Fracture : conchoidal to uneven\n\t
Crystal system : Cubic rhombic dodecahedron,icositetrahedron\n\t
Cleavage : Indistinct\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 6.5 - 7.5\n\t
Luster : vitreous to resinous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.1 - 4.3\n\t
Birefringence : None\n\t
Pleochroism : None\n\t
Refractive index : 1.72 - 1.94
</b>

    </string>
    <string name="greengarnet2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 1787.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 2337.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 2887.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 3437.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 3987.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 4537.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 5087.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 5637.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 6187.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 13475.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 14575.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 15675.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 16775.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 17875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 18975.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 20075.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 21175.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 22275.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 23375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="greenonyx">
        Green Onyx Hard, tough and durable, Green is ideal for carving and engraving or fashioning into beads, spheres and bowls, making paper weights, pen holders, book ends and boxes. Used in inexpensive jewellery Onyx is also used for stone inlay work. With its consecutive layers of different colours, it makes excellent material for cameos and some variegated pieces are used for the carving of multi-coloured figurines. Benefits: Used instead of Emerald, Green Onyx gives good comprehension power and the power to deeply analyse a situation before reacting to it. Mostly used by astrologers to give better business acumen and management skills. Who should wear it? People interested in politics should use it. It restores confidence in life and love. And though it comes in different shades like red, blue, green, yellow, black and white, but astrologically the best suited for wearing, as a ring stone is green onyx.
\n\n<b>
Green Onyx Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="greenonyx2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="greentourmaline">
        Green Tourmaline, A beautiful gem available in nearly all the colours and multi-coloured gems are also available. Its deep colours and enchanting lustre makes it one of the most widely used gemstones. Though good quality Green Tourmaline are expensive but still not as expensive as Emeralds and Rubies. Hence, Astrologers often use these as sub-stones. Benefits: Mostly green coloured Tourmaline are used in Astrology. It has a positive effect on the body and mind and does away with all the malefic influences of Rahu, Ketu, Mars and Saturn. Who should wear it? It improves memory and is very useful for children who are weak in studies also recommended for accountant, software professional etc. who are supposed to strain their mind to a very great extent. Greatly beneficial for business people, politicians and administrators.
\n\n
<b>Green Tourmaline Rs. 1100.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Cyclosilicate\n\t
Crystal system : Trigonal\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\tParallel and elongated. \n\t\tAcicular prisms, \n\t\tsometimes radiating. \n\t\tMassive. Scattered grains.\n\t
Color : \n\t\tMost commonly black, but can range from brown, violet, green, pink, or in a dual-colored pink and green.\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7–7.5\n\t
Luster : Vitreous, sometimes resinous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.06 (+.20 -.06)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.635–1.675,, 1.610–1.650\n\t
Solubility : insoluble in common solvents\n\t
Pleochroism : \n\t\tRed Tourmaline: Definite; dark red,light red Green Tourmaline: Strong; dark green, yellow-green Brown Tourmaline: Definite; dark brown, light brown Blue Tourmaline: Strong; dark blue, light blue
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="greentourmaline2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 3575.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 4675.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 6875.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 7975.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 9075.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 10175.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 11275.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 12375.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 26950.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 29150.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 31350.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 33550.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 35750.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 37950.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 40150.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 42350.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 44550.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 46750.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="iolite">
IOLITE is mined in India, Brazil, Sri Lanka, Mozambique and Brazil. It is often used as a substitute for Blue Sapphire. In Hindi, it is called KAKA NEELI - KAKA NELI because of its Blue Colour, it is related to crown chakra. People with a weak crown chakra or bad memory are advised to wear IOLITE. It is known as the GEMSTONE of self- vision, creativity and constructive ideas. IOLITE is said to have qualities of nurturing relationships. The STONE helps in healing ailments related to the digestive system, throat, nervous system and skin. It is also said to assist a person in his spiritual quest. Some scholars believe that IOLITE helps in getting knowledge about previous births.
\n\n
The low qualities of this Gem are very cheap but the good quality is rare and very difficult to procure. IOLITE GEMS above the size of 5.25 ratti is very costly.
\n\n
This is a semi-precious gem which resembles a blue sapphire. Extensively used as a substitute of Blue Sapphire. It empowers Saturn of the native said to give power on the masses and enhances the status of the person. This gem gives one an unfair advantage while dealing with the opposite sex. The superiors of the person are also positively influenced by wearing this gem.
\n\n
<b>Iolite Rs. 1100.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Silicate mineral\n\t
Crystal system : Orthorhombic - Dipyramidal \n\t
Space Group: C ccm\n\t
Crystal habit : Pseudo-hexagonal prismatic twins, as imbedded grains, and massive\n\t
Color : \n\t\tColorless, Blue, smoky blue, bluish violet; greenish, yellowish brown, gray; colorless to very pale blue in thin section\n\t
Chemical formula : (Mg,Fe)2Al4Si5O18\n\t
Twinning : Common on {110}, {130}, simple, lamellar, cyclical\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7 - 7.5\n\t
Luster : Greasy or vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Optical properties : Usually optically (-), sometimes (+); 2V = 0-90°\n\t
Refractive index : 1.527 - 1.560 , 1.532 - 1.574, 1.538 - 1.578\n\t
Fracture : Conchoidal\n\t
Cleavage : None
</b>    </string>
    <string name="iolite2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 3575.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 4675.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 6875.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 7975.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 9075.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 10175.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 11275.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 12375.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 26950.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 29150.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 31350.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 33550.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 35750.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 37950.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 40150.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 42350.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 44550.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 46750.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="jade">
Jade, It is a semi-opaque to highly translucent aggregate of juxtaposed, very firmly inter connected, granular crystals. Jade is extremely tenacious and tough. Jade is available in an enormous range of Colours, white, pink, lilac, brown, red, orange, blue, black and many shades of greet. It is used as a gem, cut into cabochons or engraved stones for settings, beads on other ornaments. It is also made into different types of decorative ware or small sculptures. Benefits: Very popular with Chinese of ancient as well as present times it is supposed to bestow long life and peaceful and protects the wearer from accidents, snake bites etc. said to be useful for those who want to have more close relationships with opposite sex. Who should wear it? Lucky gem for those born in the month of May. It is widely recommended to people suffering from allergies and skin problems.
\n\n
<b>Jade Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti. </b>
    </string>
    <string name="jade2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
</string>

    <string name="kyanite">
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 3575.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 4675.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 6875.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 7975.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 9075.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 10175.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 11275.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 12375.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 26950.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 29150.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 31350.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 33550.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 35750.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 37950.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 40150.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 42350.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 44550.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 46750.00 INR
    </string>
    <string name="labradorite2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 812.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 1062.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 1312.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 1562.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1812.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 2062.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 2312.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 2562.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 2812.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 6125.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 6625.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 7125.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 7625.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 8125.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 8625.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 9125.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 9625.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 10125.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 10625.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="lajwrat">
Lapis Lazuli, An opaque stone of blue colour with white web like structures on it, Lepiz Lazuli usually contains some traces of gold, which lends it a beautiful look. It is widely used in jewellery. Benefits: While it curtails the malefic effects of Saturn, Lepis lazuli is used to fight depression and feeling of dullness. It is effective against skin diseases and ulcers (both internal and external) and many people have faith that it has the capacity to give unqualified success to one who wears it. Who should wear it? This is especially good for ladies engaged in music, art, dance, drama etc. It gives one power to win over others by the power of love. The people who use it are never found to be wanting in money or love. Quality : Premium
<b>\n\n
Lapis Lazuli Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Rock\n\t
Crystal system : \n\t\tas lapis is a rock. Lazurite, the main constituent, frequently occurs as dodecahedra\n\t
Chemical formula : mixture of minerals\n\t
Strunz classification : 9.AF.35\n\t
Color : \n\tColorless, blue, brown, orange, gray, yellow, green, pink and reddish pink\n\t
Cleavage : none\n\t
Crystal habit : Compact, massive\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 5–5.5\n\t
Luster : dull\n\t
Streak : light blue\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.7–2.9\n\t
Refractive index : 1.5
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="lajwrat2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="lemontopaz">
       <b>Lemon Topaz Rs. 200.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Silicate mineral\n\t
Crystal symmetry : Orthorhombic dipyramidal\n\t
Chemical formula : Al2SiO4(F,OH)2\n\t
Strunz classification : 9.AF.35\n\t
Color : \n\t\tColorless, blue, brown, orange, gray, yellow, green, pink and reddish pink\n\n\t
Crystal system : Orthorhombic\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\tPrismatic crystals with faces striated parallel to long dimension; also columnar, compact, massive\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 8 (defining mineral)\n\t
Luster : Vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.606–1.629, 1.609–1.631, 1.616–1.638</b>

    </string>
    <string name="lemontopaz2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 650.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 850.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 1050.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 1250.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1450.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1650.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1850.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 2050.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 2250.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 4900.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 5300.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 5700.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 6100.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 6500.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 6900.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 7300.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 7700.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 8100.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 8500.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="malachite">
Malachite, Malachite is green in colour, but varies from mild green to almost blackish green. The tones appear in alternate stripes. Low on hardness, it may acquire exceptional polish but the polish is not very durable. Widely used for mosaics, boxes, figurines, cabochons and beads, it is also used in Jewellery. It is not very costly. Benefits: It is used to fight Kidney ailments. Malachite, if regularly worn, improves mental alertness, quickness and makes one systematic. Malachite bestows youthfulness and desire for outdoor life and aids in getting a happy life Quality : Premium
<b>\n\n
Malachite Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Carbonate mineral\n\t
Chemical formula : Al2SiO4(F,OH)2\n\t
Strunz classification : 05.BA.10\n\t
Color : \n\t\tBright green, dark green, blackish green, commonly banded in masses; green to yellowish green in transmitted light\n\n\t
Crystal system : prismatic H-M\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\tMassive, botryoidal, stalactitic, crystals are acicular to tabular prismatic\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 3.5–4.0\n\t
Luster : \n\t\tAdamantine to vitreous; silky if fibrous; dull to earthy if massive\n\t
Streak : light green\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.6–4
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (–)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.655, 1.655, 1.909</b>
    </string>
    <string name="malachite2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="opal">
        Opal is an opaque stone, with a see through surface and some minute tinges of Colours in it that give it its famous firing. Benefits: This gem is said to bestow beauty, power and financial prosperity. This improves intuition and helps magnetize others. It also helps in winning court cases and gives stability in life. Who Should Wear It: E especially good for those engaged in business connected with travel, tourism and import/export. It is an excellent gem for those born in the month of October as it turns them more loving and affectionate in personal and family life.
\n\n\n
Opal Gemstone
\n\n
Opal or Opal Gemstone is a popular Gem of Venus i.e., Shura. This Gemstone is mainly found in Australia. It is found in various varieties like White Opal, Fire Opal and Black Opal.
\n\n
Opal Gemstone if worn in silver and in accordance with the laid down procedures increases the strength of Venus and there by gives worldly pleasures. The wearer is able to get wealth, family happiness, children, fame and respect. The noted Indian film star Ashwaria Rai Bachan is always seen with this ring in her right hand index finger. It gave her stability and completeness in personal life. This gemstone has saved many marriages breaking. There are many cases in which a person has the required money or resources still he is not able to have material comforts of life, love and personal touch is simply missing. In such cases wearing an Abhimantrit Opal can bring about great change in life. I have come across many cases where this Gemstone has revived the personal lives of women and brought love and romance back.
\n\n
Artists working in TV, films, theater and the like should always wear this Gemstone for fame and recognition.
\n\n
People in whose horoscopes – Venus is Yogkarka, Ascendant Lord, Rashi Lord, or Bhagyakarka should wear an Opal Gemstone. This Gemstone does not have any side effects.
\n\n
Opal Gemstone is also widely used in Jewellery. It makes an excellent ring stone and pendant stone as its various colours allow it to be worn with any kind of cloths. Europe is the main market for Opals – the fascination of white women for opals is simply insatiable. So these Opals are found in Australia, cut and polished in India and exported in finished form to Europe.
\n\n\t
<b>White Opal      Rs. 550.00 Per Ratti
\n\n\t
Fire Opal      Rs. 1100.00 Per Ratti
\n\n\t
Black Opal      Rs. 4000.00 Per Ratti</b>

\n\n visit <b>www.astropankaj.com</b> to know :
\n
\n\tWho should wear an Opal?
\n\tBenefits of Wearing an Opal?
\n\tMantra for Opal.
\n\tHow to wear an Opal?
\n\tFinger for Opal.
\n\tWhen to wear an Opal?
\n\n\n


<b>Opal Stone
\n\n
Color : \n\t\tYellow, White, Red, Black, Green, Brown, Blue and Coloreless.\n\n\t
Fracture : Conchoidal\n\t
Crystal system : Amorphous\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 5.5–6\n\t
Luster : waxy\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.15 Refractive index : 1.42–1.43 </b>
    </string>

    <string name="peridot">
Peridot is a beautiful transparent green stone that used to be worshipped by the people of Brazil. Benefits: It enhances the power of Mercury, and thus Peridot is used to curb the problems caused by a weak mercury. The ancient Egyptian kings had immense faith in its powers and even believed that Peridot could break the evil spell and dig into the mysteries of the darkness.
<b>\n\n
Peridot Rs. 1100.00 Per Ratti, 2100.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Carbonate mineral\n\t
Crystal symmetry : Orthorhombic dipyramidal\n\t
Chemical formula : Al2SiO4(F,OH)2\n\t
Strunz classification : 9.AF.35\n\t
Color : \n\t\tColorless, blue, brown, orange, gray, yellow, green, pink and reddish pink\n\n\t
Crystal system : Orthorhombic\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\tPrismatic crystals with faces striated parallel to long dimension; also columnar, compact, massive\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 8 (defining mineral)\n\t
Luster : Vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.606–1.629, 1.609–1.631, 1.616–1.638</b>
    </string>
    <string name="peridot2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 3575.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 4675.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 6875.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 7975.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 9075.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 10175.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 11275.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 12375.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 13475.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 14575.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 15675.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 16775.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 17875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 18975.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 20075.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 21175.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 21262.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 22312.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="pinktourmaline">
       Love Gem is the common name for this Gemstone. It is said to bring genuine love in life.Couples that have problems in relationships can get immense benefit if both of them wear it. Pink Turmuline looks beautiful is said to bring beauty to life.
\n\n
<b>Pink Tourmaline Rs. 1100.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Cyclosilicate\n\t
Crystal system : Trigonal\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\tParallel and elongated. Acicular prisms, sometimes radiating. Massive. Scattered grains.\n\n\t
Color : \n\t\tMost commonly black, but can range from brown, violet, green, pink, or in a dual-colored pink and green.\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7–7.5\n\t
Luster : Vitreous, sometimes resinous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.06 (+.20 -.06)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.635–1.675,, 1.610–1.650\n\t
Solubility : insoluble in common solvents\n\t
Pleochroism :</b> \n\tRed Tourmaline: \n\t\tDefinite; dark red,light red \n\n\tGreen Tourmaline: \n\t\tStrong; dark green, yellow-green \n\n\tBrown Tourmaline: \n\t\tDefinite; dark brown, light brown \n\n\tBlue Tourmaline: \n\t\tStrong; dark blue, light blue
    </string>
    <string name="pinktourmaline2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 3575.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 4675.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 6875.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 7975.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 9075.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 10175.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 11275.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 12375.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 26950.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 29150.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 31350.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 33550.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 35750.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 37950.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 40150.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 42350.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 44550.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 46750.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="redonyx1">
<b>Red Onyx Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti. </b>
    </string>
    <string name="redonyx2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="rhodolite">
        <b>Rhodolite Garnet Rs.2100.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n
Rhodolite Garnet is a species of garnet family. It is found in Macon which is located in North Carolina in Cowee Valley.
\n\n\t
        <b>Category : Pyrope variety\n\t
Chemical formula : (Mg,Fe)3Al2(SiO4)3\n\t
Cleavage : none, may show indistinct parting\n\t
Color : light to dark purplish red through reddish purple\n\t
Crystal system : cubic\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\tPrismatic crystals with faces striated parallel to long dimension; also columnar, compact, massive\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7 - 7.5\n\t
Luster : greasy to vitreous\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.84 (+/- .10)\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.760 (+.010, -.020)</b>
    </string>

    <string name="rosequartz">
<b>Rose Quartz Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
        \n\n\t
<b>Category : Silicate mineral\n\t
Crystal symmetry : Trigonal H–M Symbol 32\n\t
Chemical formula : Silica (silicon dioxide, SiO2)\n\t
Strunz classification : 04.DA.05\n\t
Color : \n\t\tColorless, From colorless to black, through various colors\n\n\t
Crystal system : trapezohedral class 3 2\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\t6-sided prism ending in 6-sided pyramid (typical), drusy, fine-grained to microcrystalline, massive\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7 – lower in impure\n\t
Luster : Vitreous – waxy to dull when massive\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.65; variable 2.59–2.63 in impure varieties\n\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent to nearly opaque\n\t
Optical properties : Uniaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.543–1.545, 1.552–1.554</b>
    </string>
    <string name="rosequartz2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="starruby">
Star Ruby is never completely transparent, because the star can only be produced by the presence of needle like inclusions that cause some degree of turbidity. Star rubies are very valuable. The finest star ruby known weighs 138 carats; this is the famous Rosier Reeves star ruby, on display at the Smithsonian Institution in Washington, D.C. The most striking phenomenon of rubies is the development of the six ray star, arranged in perfect symmetry, which shifts its centre, as the stone is moved. It is clearly visible under a single light source such as the sun or a lamp; much less so in diffuse light. If two or more powerful light sources are set close together, as many stars can be seen in the stone. Each light produces its own star, which is basically a reflection. The effect is usually less pronounced in more transparent stones. When the ground colour is ruby red it is known as Star Ruby. Benefits: Used to pep up the internal strength and to ward off tensions, Star Ruby drives away stress related problems like Migraine, Insomnia, and Hysteria etc. Traditionally worn by knights in the battlefields to protect themselves from the enemy. Local tales in Karnataka say that if this is worn as a visible pendant or as a head gear then anyone who faces you, as an enemy looses half his valour to your. It is said that Karna, the son of Sun wore it in his head gear and only after Krishna directed Arjuna to remove the Headgear with his arrow was be able to fight an equal battle with him.
\n\n<b>
Star Ruby Rs. 525.00 Per Rati. </b>
    </string>
    <string name="starruby2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 1706.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 2231.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 2756.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 3281.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 3806.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 4331.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 4856.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 5381.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 5906.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 12862.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 13912.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 14962.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 16012.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 17062.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 18112.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 19162.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 20212.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 21262.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 22312.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="maryam">
<b>
Sang E Maryam Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti. </b>
    </string>
    <string name="maryam2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="tigerseye">
Tiger\'s Eye consists of compact fibers of quartz that has replaced asbestos fibers. The light reflected from the fibers produces a strong sheen or silky appearance, like that of the original asbestos known as \'Chiromancy\'. The result is a series of minor gemstones differing only in their ground Colour and that of mobile reflection. A golden yellow reflection on a brown ground is called a Tiger\'s Eye. It may very from brown and brownish yellow to blue and blue grey. The Colours and clearly fibrous appearance once are normally distinctive. Despite its attractiveness, this material is not very valuable. Benefits: It is normally cut on cabochon, to bring out the chiromancy, but it can be cut into more or less round, polished pieces, for necklaces and pendants. Tiger\'s Eye is also used for carvings, boxes, ashtrays, and other ornamental items, although in these, the fibers are seen as strips of colour. Said to be a Gem that gives courage and self confidence. Widely used in Africa toward off evil eye and to give the wearer victory over his enemies. Who should wear it? The evil spirits stay away for the wearer of this gem. It improves energy and stamina and gives inner initiative and drive. Recommended for those with birth No. 2 or 7.
\n\n
<b>Tiger\'s Eye Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n\t
Category : Mineral\n\t
Chemical formula : Silica (silicon dioxide, SiO2)\n\t
Color : golden to red-brown\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7.0\n\t
Luster : Silky\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.64 – 2.71
    </string>
    <string name="tigerseye2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="feroja3">
        <b>Tarquoise Rs. 350.00 Per Ratti.</b>
        \n\n\t
<b>Category : Phosphate minerals\n\t
Chemical formula : CuAl6(PO4)4(OH)8·4H2O\n\t
Strunz classification : 08.DD.15\n\t
Color : Blue, blue-green, green\n\t
Crystal system : Triclinic\n\t
Crystal habit : Massive, nodular\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 5-7\n\t
Luster : Waxy to subvitreous\n\t
Streak : Bluish white\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.6-2.9\n\t
Pleochroism : Weak\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.610, 1.615, 1.650</b>
    </string>

    <string name="whitecoral">
        This is used with considerable success in problems which are difficult to understand by the doctors. This gives a person capacity to speak with authority and its regular facial expression. This also helps in the strength to bear unpleasant happenings and understand the working of other people\'s minds.
\n\n<b>
White Coral Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti. </b>
    </string>
    <string name="whitecoral2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="whitequartz">
White Qurtz is a plain white stone, which lacks a bit in luster but makes up for it in its extreme clarity; it also gives out a unique shine. Benefits: It has a cooling and soothing effect on one who\'s both looking on and wearing it. If worn in such a way that it touches the skin then it cools down the person and gives him inner peace. s Who should wear it? This gem has the highest occult power and is used extensively by Sadhus and other people who want to get special heavenly powers. It is useful in combating stress-related problems if worn in 50 ct. plus sizes.
\n\n<b>
White Quartz Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Silicate mineral\n\t
Crystal symmetry : Trigonal H–M Symbol 32\n\t
Strunz classification : 04.DA.05\n\t
Color : \n\t\tFrom colorless to black, through various colors\n\n\t
Crystal system : \n\tquartz: trigonal trapezohedral class 3 2; \n\tquartz: hexagonal 622\n\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\t6-sided prism ending in 6-sided pyramid (typical), drusy, fine-grained to microcrystalline, massive\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 7 – lower in impure\n\t
Luster : Vitreous – waxy to dull when massive\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 2.65; variable 2.59–2.63 in impure varieties\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Uniaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.543–1.545, 1.552–1.554 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="whitequartz2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="whiterainbow">
<b>White Rainbow Rs. 150.00 Per Ratti. </b>
    </string>
    <string name="whiterainbow2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 487.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 637.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 787.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 937.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 1087.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 1237.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 1387.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 1537.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 1687.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 3675.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 3975.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 4275.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 4575.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 4875.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 5175.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 5475.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 5775.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 6075.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 6375.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="whitetopaz">
<b>White Topaz Rs. 350.00 Per Ratti.
\n\n\t
Category : Silicate mineral\n\t
Crystal symmetry : Orthorhombic dipyramidal\n\t
Strunz classification : 9.AF.35\n\t
Color : \n\t\tColorless, blue, brown, orange, gray, yellow, green, pink and reddish pink\n\n\t
Crystal system : Orthorhombic\n\t
Crystal habit : \n\t\tPrismatic crystals with faces striated parallel to long dimension; also columnar, compact, massive\n\n\t
Mohs scale hardness : 8 (defining mineral)\n\t
Luster : Vitreous\n\t
Streak : White\n\t
Specific gravity : 3.49–3.57\n\t
Diaphaneity : Transparent\n\t
Optical properties : Biaxial (+)\n\t
Refractive index : 1.606–1.629, 1.609–1.631, 1.616–1.638</b>
    </string>
    <string name="whitetopaz2">
        <b>Weight : INR</b>\n\t
        3.25 Ratti Rs. 1137.00 INR\n\t4.25 Ratti Rs. 1487.00 INR\n\t5.25 Ratti Rs. 1837.00 INR\n\t6.25 Ratti Rs. 2187.00 INR\n\t7.25 Ratti Rs. 2537.00 INR\n\t8.25 Ratti Rs. 2887.00 INR\n\t9.25 Ratti Rs. 3237.00 INR\n\t10.25 Ratti Rs. 3587.00 INR\n\t11.25 Ratti Rs. 3937.00 INR\n\t12.25 Ratti Rs. 8575.00 INR\n\t13.25 Ratti Rs. 9275.00 INR\n\t14.25 Ratti Rs. 9975.00 INR\n\t15.25 Ratti Rs. 10675.00 INR\n\t16.25 Ratti Rs. 11375.00 INR\n\t17.25 Ratti Rs. 12075.00 INR\n\t18.25 Ratti Rs. 12775.00 INR\n\t19.25 Ratti Rs. 13475.00 INR\n\t20.25 Ratti Rs. 14175.00 INR\n\t21.25 Ratti Rs. 14875.00 INR
    </string>

    <string name="zircon">
Zircon (AD):\n Looks like diamond and shines more than it. But unlike diamond, it shines only for a flash of a second, after which it looks dull and pale. Widely used in astrology as a substitute of diamond, Zircon is said to enhance beauty and attractiveness of a person. It makes an excellent ring stone and is thus widely used in jewellery also. Benefits: It gives added popularity in social circles and appreciation by members of the opposite sex. It improves prestige and protects him from jealousies and rivalries and plots hatched by one\'s enemies Quality : Premium
\n\n
Zircon is found many coloures like red, pink, yellow, or black. Zircon may also be coloreless.
\n\n
<b>Zircon (AD) Rs. 110.00 Per Ratti.</b>
\n\n
Natural Zircon
\n\n
Name:
        \nFrom the Arabic "zar", gold, plus "gun", coloured, referring to one of the many colors that the mineral may display.\n\n
Dimorph of: Reidite\n\t
Formula: ZrSiO4\n\t
System: Tetragonal\n\t
Member of: Zircon Group\n\t
Lustre: Adamantine, Vitreous, Greasy\n\t
Colour: \n\t\tColourless, yellow, grey, reddish-brown, green, brown, black,\n\n\t
Hardness: 7.5\n\t
        \n\n
Zircon is found in the most metamorphic rocks as small crystals mostly widely distributed and rarely more than 1% of the total mass of the rock.
\n\n
<b>Natural Zircon Rs. 2100.00 Per Ratti.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="software_dev">Made with ❤️ by International Orgaisation Of Software Developers</string>
    <string name="hara_pukhraj_head">HARA PUKHRAJ | GREEN SAPPHIRE</string>
    <string name="baingani_pukhraj_head">BAINGANI PUKHRAJ | PURPLE SAPPHIRE</string>
    <string name="gulabi_pukhraj_head">GULABI PUKHRAJ | PINK SAPPHIRE</string>
    <string name="moti_head">MOTI | PEARL</string>
    <string name="pitambari_neelam_head">PUTAMBARI NEELAM | YELLOW BLUE SAPPHIRE</string>
    <string name="safed_pukhraj_head">SAFED PUKHRAJ | WHITE SAPPHIRE</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="custom_channel_name">Push Notifications Channel</string>


    <!--<string name="order_id">Order Id : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="customer_id">Customer Id : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="transaction_amount">Transaction Amount : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="channel_id">Channel Id : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="industry_type_id">Industry Type Id : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="website">Website : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="theme">Theme : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="cust_email_id">Email Id : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="cust_mobile_no">Mobile Number : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="merchant_id">Merchant Id : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="checksum_generation_url">Checksum Generation URL : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="checksum_verification_url">Checksum Verification URL : </string>-->
    <!--<string name="start_transaction">Start Transaction</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_order_id">ORDER</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_customer_id">CUST23657</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_transaction_amount">1</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_channel_id">WAP</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_industry_type_id">Retail</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_website">worldpressplg</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_theme">merchant</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_cust_email_id">abc@gmail.com</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_cust_mobile_no">123</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_merchant_id_staging">WorldP64425807474247</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_checksum_generation_url">https://pguat.paytm.com/merchant-chksum/ChecksumGenerator</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sample_checksum_verification_url">https://pguat.paytm.com/merchant-chksum/ValidateChksum</string>-->

    <string name="title_activity_new_web_view">NewWebView</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_astrology">AstrologyActivity</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>