<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GemSelections</string>
    <string name="tv_payment_1">
        YOU MAY DEPOSIT <b>CHEQUE OR DD </b> ELECTRONIC TRANSFER TO: \n\n
        Khanna Gems Private Limited,\n
        Punjab and Sindh Bank,\n
        <b>A/c No. 08681300000642</b>\n
        <b>IFSC Code: PSIB0000963</b>
    </string>
    <string name="tv_payment_2">
        PAY BY USING\n
        <b>www.paypal.com</b>\n
        to\n
        <b>care@khannagems.com</b>
    </string>
    <string name="tv_payment_3">
        SEND A CHEQUE IN FAVOUR OF\n
        <b>Khanna Gems Private Limited</b>\n\n
        SHOP NO. 8, A-3 DDA MARKET\n
        Janakpuri,\n
        New Delhi - 110058\n
        (Near St. Marks School)
    </string>
    <string name="delivery_message">We deliver anywhere in the World.\n\nThrough the 25 years of its existence Gem Selections has consistently delivered quality and that too at most reasonable prices.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">GemSelections</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="tag_1">(A Unit of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited)</string>
    <string name="tag_2">“Gem Stones is our religion”  \n– Gem Selections</string>

    <string name="about_us">
        Gem Selections came into being on 13th day of January 1987 as a proprietary concern. Its main line of business was buying raw Gem stones from the mines and getting them cut and polished (Lapidary Work) and then supplying these Gems to various Jewellers across India.
        \n\n
        In 1994 it set up a wholesale and retail outlet in JanakPuri,New Delhi and has been handling its marketing operations from there since then. In addition to selling Gemstones it also started manufacturing and selling Diamond and Gem studded Jewellery and Handicrafts made of Semi-Precious and Rough Gems, Rudraksha and other related products.
        \n\n
        In 1997, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited took over Gem Selections with Pankaj Khanna and Anu Khanna as its Directors.
        \n\n
        Judging the value and quality of Gem Stones requires specialised knowledge, training and experience. We at Gem Selections, are dedicated to the highest standards of ethics in helping our customers choose the right Gem Stones which are of the highest quality at the most affordable prices.We regularly update our market information and are always updated about whatever is new in the field of Gem Stones, Diamonds, Jewellery and our other trade products.
        \n\n
        It is the endeavor of Gem Selections to become a benchmark of quality and customer satisfaction in every field of its operations.
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited was incorporated on 20th January,1997 and on 1st April,1997 it took over Gem Selections. Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited deals in retail and wholesale of Gemstones, Diamonds, Jewellery, Handirafts, Rudraksha and other related products. In July 2002 Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited became the back end for all the Gemstones, Rudraksha and Yantra requirements of the Times Internet Limited (www.astrospeak.com). In addition to Times Internet Limited we have been the back end for Gem Stone requirements for www.rediff.com , www.indiainfo.com , www.homeshop18.com , www.sirindia.com .
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited is the only company in India that sells Gemstones with proper Govt. Lab Certificate, be it our brick and mortar shop in Janakpuri or our websites www.khannagems.com and www.gemselections.in. Each and every Gemstone that we sell goes through rigorous testing first at the company level and then we get each and every Gemstone certified by IGI – GTL. Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited assures thequality and transparency in the field of Gemstones.
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited has also been the backend for handicrafts for HHEC since 2007 and Taj Khazana stores in Goa and Mumbai since 2008.
        \n\n
        The guiding principal of the company have been the words of Peter F Drucker “It is the credit the reputation for honest dealings and the dependability of the businessman on which depends his ultimate success or otherwise.” With this ideal the company developed a vast base of 100% satisfied customers not only across the length and breadth of India but also in foreign lands.
        \n\n\n
        <b><i>Vision – To be the global benchmark for quality and be the biggest player in Gemstones, Diamonds and Jewellery Industry.</i></b>
    </string>

    <string name="management_head"><u>MANAGEMENT TEAM</u></string>
    <string name="management_team">
        <b>Pankaj Khanna – Director, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited</b>
        \n\n
        Pankaj Khanna is the founder of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited and has been the Director of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited since its incorporation in 1997. He is a commerce graduate for Sri Venketeshwara College, Delhi University and Life Member of All India Management Association. He completed a Certificate Course in Gemology from Surat Gemology Institute (Regd.) in March 1986. He is a Life Member of Indian Diamond Institute, Surat since 2004 and has been authorized by Indian Institution of Valuers, Pune to use the title of “Chartered Valuer of Jewellery”. He is aLife Member of Consultancy Development Centre, New Delhi
        \n\n
        Pankaj Khanna is also a renowned astrologer and has appeared in approximately 100 episodes of Star Plus program ‘Meri Sehali’ and 60 episodes of E TV program ‘Nari’. Apart from television he has also been widely covered by numerous TV channels including, CNBC, Star News and by national newspapers like The Hindustan Times and The Times of India.
        \n\n

        <b>Anu Khanna – Director, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited</b>
        \n\n
        Anu Khanna has been the Director of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited since its incorporation in 1997. She is M.Com with specialisation in Finance and Taxation from Delhi University. She has been involved in Gem and Jewellery trade since 1990.
        \n\n
        <b>Anubha Khanna – Jewellery Designer, </b>
        \n\n
        She is an artist and creates unique jewellery designs out of Gemstones and Diamonds for Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited.
        \n\n
        <b>Aaradhya Khanna – Trainee,</b>
        \n\n
        Aaradhya Khanna is a trainee at Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited. He is learning the art and science of handling Gem trade.
        \n\n\n
        <b>A strange love story…</b>
        \n\n
        Pankaj Khanna had a strange fascination for Gemstones and Jewellery. Even as a young child Pankaj Khanna used to visit jewellers and used to see their show – windows from outside. He always wanted to do this trade from the childhood but had no knowledge and family background for the same. He did his graduation from Sri Venketeshwara College, Delhi University and then he went to Surat to formally study Gemology and lived there for one year and did a certificate course in Gemology and wanted to start Gemstones business fulltime. He started his business venture with a meagre amount of Rs.1000 in 13th day of January 1987.
        \n\n
        But simultaneously he had given competitive exams due to social dogmaand was selected in NTPC, a public sector undertaking. He joined NTPC on 5th March 1987.
        \n\n
        But his heart pulled him away and in March 1994 he left the job and ventured full time into his cherished business. He started the business as a supplier to Jewellers and Astrologers across North India.
        \n\n
        In 1997, he founded Khanna Gems Private Limited dealing in retail and wholesale of Gemstones, Diamonds, Jewellery, Handirafts, Rudraksha and yantras.Pankaj Khanna while handling the Gemstones business became a celebrity Astrologer and after the closing the shop in the evening used to work as in-house Astrologer with Taj Mahal Hotel (Taj Group of Hotels), New Delhi and with ITC Maurya Sheraton (Welcome Group), New Delhi. Mr. Khanna has also appeared in approximately 60 episodes of Star Plus program ‘Meri Sehali’ and 60 episodes of E TV program ‘Nari’, where he educated the masses about the various astrological concepts and products. Apart from television he has also been widely covered by numerous TV channels including, CNBC, Star News and by national Newspapers like The Hindustan Times and The Times of India. In 2002
        \n\n
        Even with limited resources and locational disadvantage Pankaj Khanna with his entrepreneurial skills has managed to create Gem Selections as a brand in the field of Gemstones in India.
        \n\n
        He is a Life Member of All India Management Association He is a Life Member of Indian Diamond Institute, Surat since 2004 and has been authorized by Indian Institution of Valuers, Pune to use the title of “Chartered Valuer of Jewellery”. He is a Life Member of Consultancy Development Centre, New Delhi
        \n\n
        In July 2002 Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited became the back end for all the Gemstones, Rudraksha and Yantra requirements of the Times Internet Limited.In addition to Times Internet Limited, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited has been the back end for Gemstones requirements for www.rediff.com , www.indiainfo.com , www.homeshop18.com , www.sirindia.com . Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited is the only company in India that sells Gemstones with proper Govt. Lab Certificate, be it our brick and mortar shop in Janakpuri or our websites www.khannagems.com and www.gemselections.in. Each and every Gemstone that we sell goes through rigorous testing first at the company level and then we get each and every Gemstone certified by IGI – GTL. Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited is the benchmark for quality and transparency in the field of Gemstones.
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited has also been the backend for handicrafts for HHEC since 2007 and Taj Khazana stores in Goa and Mumbai since 2008.
    </string>
    <string name="_pankaj">
        Sh. Pankaj Khanna who is a renowned Astrologer is also a Certified Gemologist and Jewellery Valuer. He has strived hard all his life so that people are able to get: \n
        \n\t\t 1. Original Gemstones.
        \n\t\t 2. Gemstones with a high efficacy.
        \n\t\t 3. Gemstones that are property abhimantrit and charged.
        \n\t\t 4. Gemstones that come with full disclosure as to any treatment or enhancement.
    </string>
    <string name="_khanna_gems">
        <b>Khanna Gems Private Limited</b> Started its Operations on 1st – April – 1997 by taking over the business of Gem Selections a 10 years old firm.
        \n\n
        The Core Business of Khanna Gems Private Limited it to procure rough Gemstones from mines and then cut and polish them.
        \n\n
        All varieties of Precious and Semi-Precious Gemstones are dealt with at Khanna Gems Private Limite.
        \n\n
        The Gemstones are checked for purity, efficacy and superior cutting and then send to Govt. Lab of Gem and Jewellery Export Promotion council for certification.
        \n\n
        The entire inventory at Khanna Gems Private Limited is Govt. Lab Certified.
        \n\n
        The Khanna Gems Private Limited is known for quality and originality of its Gemstones and dependability of it dealings.
        \n\n
        <b><i>Our Motto: Original Gemstones always and every time.</i></b>
    </string>
    <string name="frag_home_1">We also make rings and pendants</string>
    <string name="copyright">© KHANNA GEMS PVT. LTD.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_rudraksha">Rudraksha</string>

    <string name="_rud_mantra">
        One Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Two Mukhi \t<b>(Om Namah)</b>\n\n
        Three Mukhi \t<b>(Kali Namah)</b>\n\n
        Four Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Five Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Six Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Seven Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Eight Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Nine Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Ten Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Eleven Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Twelve Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Thirteen Mukhi \t<b>(Om Shrom Namah)</b>\n\n
        Fourteen Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Gauri Shankar \t<b>(Om Namah Shivai)</b>\n\n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="_rud_how_to_wear">
        The scared Rudhraksha that you have got is abhimantrit and empowered by Pankaj Khanna, so that it gives maximum results. This is ready to wear or can be kept in your place of worship and should be worn on a Monday morning before 7.30 a.m.
        \n\n
        To recharge it, you should take it off one week before Mahashivratri. Take a clean bowl and put the Rudraksha in it. Add Pure Desi Ghee in that bowl so that the Rudhraksha is properly immersed in it. Add some sandal wood powder, a bit of turmeric powder (Haldi) in that bowl. Leave it for a week’s time or more.
        \n\n
        Then on Mahashivratri day before 7.30 a.m. wash it with Ganga Jal mixed with saffron (kesar) and wear it after chanting the required mantra 108 times. Fasting on Mondays and Mahashivratri day will also be great help and improves the results from a Rudraksha.
    </string>
    <string name="_rud_auth">
        The Mystic bead Rudhraksha is highly sacred to the Hindus of all castes / sects and regions. But as some of the Rudhraksha are very costly so some people out of greed try to tamper with the Rudhraksha so as to make them like a more costly member of the family.
        \n\n
        <b>Now, the question before the buyer is how he should check the authenticity of the Rudhraksha.</b>
        \n\n\n
        <b>1. EYE TEST:</b> Look at the bead all the mukhas / faces should look like joined lips and the partitions where the line is visible should be clear and look natural.
        \n\n
        <b>2. EYE GLASS:</b> Sometimes Rudhraksha are faked by removing the thorn like parts from one piece and then sticking it to another. This can be judged by a close examination by a 10x Lens.
        \n\n
        <b>3. WATER TEST:</b> Put the Rudhraksha in boiling water and let it remain there for 20 – 30 minutes. If some faces are tempered with them they shall come off as the glue – fevicol or the like will come off.
        \n\n
        <b>4. SCIENTIFIC TEST:</b> A botanical laboratory or a botanist can test a Rudhraksha and testify its originality. So, if in doubt take the Rudhraksha to a Botanical laboratory and know the facts.
    </string>
    <string name="_rud_faqs">
        <b>1. How can, this mystic power named Rudhraksha, be used by mankind for maximum benefit?</b>
        \n\n
        \tRudhraksha can either be worn in neck or it can be at a sacred place in house i.e., in the puja room or in front of God’s / Goddess’s idol or picture.
        \n\n
        <b>2. Should Rudhraksha be worn all the time?</b>
        \n\n
        \tIf one chooses to wear a Rudhraksha then he/she should wear it all the day and take off before going to bed. Then it should be worn again after the morning puja / prayers.
        \n\n
        <b>3. Can one eat non-vegetarian food and take alcohol if one is wearing Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \tThough taking non-vegetarian food and alcohol is not recommended to keep the Sanchit Karma pure but the Shiva sect of Hindu religion of which Rudhraksha is a symbol – does not prohibit it. So, one can take non-vegetarian food and take alcohol while wearing Rudhraksha.
        \n\n
        <b>4. What is the greatest use of Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \tRudhraksha beads regulate the blood pressure thus helping in controlling the thought process. This helps in Meditations which is the ultimate tool to realize the power of the inner self.
        \n\n
        <b>5. Does wearing Rudhraksha bring results?</b>
        \n\n
        \tThough one of the most sacred possessions of a Hindu – Rudhraksha does not lead to instant results but if worn over a period of time with complete faith and the required mantras are chanted regularly then the results promised by the Mahashiv Purana are surely achieved – this is what the sages say.
        \n\n
        <b>6. What is the cost of one Mukhi Round Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \tOne Mukhi Round Rudhraksha, which is said to have extraordinary powers is often heard of but such a piece is not seen in trade – I have never come across such a piece which is original, though I am trading in them since 1987.
        \n\n
        <b>7. How else can we get the benefits of Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \t(1) Rudhraksha can be kept in the place of worship.
        \n
        \t(2) One can dip seven beads of five Mukhi Rudhraksha in a glass of water and drink the water daily in the morning. This improves the blood circulation, gives one better concentration and the general nervous system in improved. The Rudhraksha beads have to be changed after every seven days.
    </string>

    <string name="_bracelet">
        <b>Rudraksha Bracelet</b>
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 1100.00</b>
        \n\n
        \tThe birth of son in the family gives it strength and continuity. The couples who desire that a son should be born to them should wear it. This not only helps in birth of a male offspring but also helps in giving his long life and strength.
        \n\n\n
        <b>\tThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
        Rs. 1100.00
    </string>
    <string name="_bracelet_two">
        <b>Two Mukhi Rudraksha Bracelet</b>
        \n\n
        \tThis fulfills desires and cuts down the problems and impediments created by the Government or superiors. It raises a person to a very high level and leadership qualities are developed by its constant use
        \n\n\n
        <b>\tThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
Rs.     <b>Rs. 1000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_bracelet_three">
        <b>Three Mukhi Rudraksha Bracelet</b>
        \n\n
        \tThis fulfills desires and cuts down the problems and impediments created by the Government or superiors. It raises a person to a very high level and leadership qualities are developed by its constant use.
        \n\n\n
        \t<b>The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
       <b>Rs. 1000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_bracelet_four">
        <b>Rudraksha Pearl Combination</b>
        \n\n
        \tThis string is Natural Fresh Water Pearls. Pearl beads are very good for chanting the name of Vishnu and all his incarnations. It improves the glow in the skin and makes it vibrant. It improves the natural beauty of the wearer. This string improves the imagination, power of expression and the skill of handling people.
        \n\n
        \tThis is a rosary which is used to chant the name of Lord Shiva . It gives peace of mind ,controls the blood pressure and also strengthens the mind . In Ayurveda this is used to cure epilepsy .This mala is widely used to awaken the Kundalini Shakti .
        \n\n
        <b>\tThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
        <b>Rs. 501.00 </b>
    </string>

    <string name="_mala1">TWO MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 41550.00</string>
    <string name="_mala2">
        Two Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the basis of this universe. The benefits that a person derives from the use of this Rudraksha are akin to those derived from AGNI PUJA. In astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Moon Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        Two Mukhi Rudraksha mantra
        \n\n
        Two Mukhi (Om Namah)
        \n\n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 41550.00
    </string>
    <string name="_mala3">THREE MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 21000.00</string>
    <string name="_mala4">
        Three Mukhi Rudraksha mala is a symbol of Brahma, Vishnu and Mahesh. This is considered to be the cause of creation of the three worlds. This curtails the destructive forces within a person and evolves his creativity. This removes the malefic effects of Mars. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 21000.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala5">FOUR MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 2650.00</string>
    <string name="_mala6">
        Four Mukhi Rudraksha Mala gives results in all the four dimensions of human endeavour; i.e., Dharm, Arth, Kama and Moksha. Wearing this helps in reducing mental problems. In astrology this is said to remove the malefic effects of Mercury. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 2650.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala7">FIVE MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 600.00</string>
    <string name="_mala8">
        Paach Mukhi Rudraksha Mala (five mukhi ) This is a rosary which is used to chant the name of Lord Shiva . It gives peace of mind ,controls the blood pressure and also strengthens the mind . In Ayurveda this is used to cure epilepsy .This mala is widely used to awaken the Kundalini Shakti .
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala9">SIX MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 2650.00</string>
    <string name="_mala10">
        Six Mukhi Rudraksha Mala is a form of Kartika and Ganesha. This awakens the sleeping powers of an individual. By wearing this, a person imbibes moral strength, will power and the power of knowledge. This has the complete blessings of Gauri Mata. It gives a person the gift of comprehension. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Venus. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 2650.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala11">SEVEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 10000.00</string>
    <string name="_mala12">
        Seven Mukhi Rudraksha Mala is said to be dear to Kamdev and is also known by his name. This is also considered to be the form Devi Shakti and Nag Shakti. If it\'s a woman\'s affections you are hoping to attract, the Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is exactly what you need. The beads are known to make the wearer irresistible to the female of the species. This is said to remove the malefic effects of Saturn Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 10000.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala13">EIGHT MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 8300.00</string>
    <string name="_mala14">
        Eight Mukhi Rudraksha Mala is a form of Ganesha. This protects the person from problems related to litigation. This also saves one from accidents and potent enemies. The wearer does not get agitated and controls the mind. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Rahu. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>

    <string name="_yugal1">Aakarshan Vriddhi Yantra</string>
    <string name="_yugal2">
    Aakarshan Vriddhi Yantra. (AVY08) Cleopatra was known to wear magnets on her body and that helped her to attract the opposite sex. Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is manifestation of Kamdev and pearl is the Gem of Beauty these there in. Combination can gives you an unfore advantage in attracting the opposite sex and retaining it. Men and Women of all age groups can use it. Advantageously
        \n\nThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 6000.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal3">Laxmi Vardhak Yugal\n\nRs. 2100.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal4">
    Laxmi Vardhak Yugal. (LVY02) Rudraksha Combination for Wealth (Laxmi Vardhak Yugal) : Six Mukhi Rudraksha has the powers of Venus it gives wealth. Laxmiji resides where Six Mukhi is kept. In combination with Four Mukhi Rudraksha which is the manifestation of Genesha and Emerald which brings all kinds of wealth and makes it stable. If this combination is worn regularly and Laxmi Strota is recited daily then all wants of the person are automatically fulfilled and he is never seen in a state of dissatisfaction.
    \n\nThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    \n\n
    <b>Rs. 2100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal5">Raktachap Niyantran Raj Yog Yugal</string>
    <string name="_yugal6">
        Raktachap Niyantran tatha Rajya such Yugal. (RNT06) Sun is the regulator of heart and blood stream in combination with Rudraksha it is said to give special efforts. It also help in giving better status in service and gives the support of the government and seniors. Rudraksha Mala, 7.25 Rati Ruby Surya lockets made of 92.5% Pure Silver with Surya Mantra Engraved on it.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 3100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal7">Sarve Manokamana Prapti Yugal \n\nRs. 2100.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal8">
        Sarve Manokamana Prapti Yugal. (SMY09) Life is short and the desires of mankind are multiple. The planet Jupiter is said to give earthly pleasures and also salvation after death. Sarva Mano – Kamna Prapti Yugal empowers Jupiter and gives all that a man desires in life. It contains 3.25 rt Golden Topaz made in silver with Guru Mantra inscribed on it strung in a thread with two beads of the mighty Five Mukhi Rudraksha. It should be regularly worn and the mantra of Jupiter ‘Om ! Gram Greem Groom Sah Guruve Namah’ should be regularly chanted to strengthen Jupiter and for fulfilment of all desires.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 2100.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="_yugal9">Shatru Nashak Yugal \n\nRs.1550.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal10">
        Shatru Nashak Yugal. (SNY03) Rudraksha Combination to Win Over Enemies (Shatru Nashak Yugal): All successful people have to face enemies created by envy. Enemies not only try to harm you by various means but also steel your peace of mind. Various Vedic prayers and Tantric rituals are available for steeling a victory over ones enemies. Shatru Nashak Rudraksha Yugal is aimed at puncturing the power base of the people having ill feelings or enmity towards you. It weakens there resolve and creates problems for them so that instead of putting there mind on creating problems for you they get busy fighting for there own survival.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 1550.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="_yugal11">Sukhi Bhav Yugal\n\nRs. 2100.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal12">
        Sukhi Bhav Yugal. (SBY05) Rudraksha Combination for Betterment of Married Life / Love (Sukhi Bhav Yugal) : All wealth, fame, success and achievements seem useless for a person who does not get love in life, instead of happiness there is a constant state of depression. To overcome these problems one should wear this Yugal. If one wears it regularly and chants Gayatri Mantra he/she gets love from the cherished members of opposite sex giving a sense of fulfilment.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 2100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal13">Vidya Vardhak Yugal\n\nRs. 5100.00 </string>
    <string name="_yugal14">
        Vidya Vardhak Yugal. (VVY01) Rudraksha Combination for Education (Vidya Vardhak Yugal) This Rudraksha combination (Yugal) improves the level of concentration, retentive power and restrains the mind from being deverted towards Maya created by the various Rajasik and Tamsik powers (shakties) of nature. The results that the students get by wearing this combination are simply amazing. There retentive power and intelligence level improves leading to better grades.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 5100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal15">Vijaye Bhav Yugal\n\nRs. 11000.00 </string>
    <string name="_yugal16">
        Vijaye Bhav Yugal. (VBY04) Rudraksha Combination to get Professional Rise (Vijaye Bhav Yugal) Nothing succeeds like success is a truth known to all of us but our efforts are not always rewarded and we all often feel that there are certain cosmic powers which must support our efforts in order to give us a lasting success. Vijaye Bhav Yugal helps in getting support of these powers. If this Yugal is constantly worn and the mantra ‘Om Namah Shivae’ is regularly chanted then the efforts of the person are invariably crowned with success.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 11000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal17">Vyapar Vridhi Karja Mukti Yugal\n\nRs. 5100.00 </string>
    <string name="_yugal18">
        Vyapar Vridhi Karja Mukti Yugal. (VVK07) Emerals ie, Morkat mani or Panna is the Gem of lord Ganesha this Gem gives enhancement of wealth and success in Business ventures in combination with the Rudraksha of Budh the Four Mukhi Rudraksha it gives Instant results. It is a must for people who want to rice in Business and make their Enjoining or future venture a Success. Two Four Mukhi Rudraksha With 7.25 rati Emeralds in 92.5% Pure Silver Yantra With Budh Mantra Engraved on in.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 5100.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="tag_3">\" The Message \n\" Rudraksha – \nFrom Lord Shiva with Love</string>
    <string name="_rud_home">
    <b>Why Rudraksha - At the First Stage ?</b>\n\n\t
The human life is full of pain both on the physical as well as emotional level. Our ancient Rishis tried to search for cures for all ailments that effect us . These cures were in the form of Auyerveda , religion etc . But even with a healthy body and complete devotion to God man does not feel happy and to large extent all his efforts after fulfillment of basic bread and butter needs are aimed at searching for that happiness. He wanders in search of this happiness in Disco Thiks and nightclubs or else in Rishikesh or temples ………….. he tries to earn extraordinary money, be a leader but all this leaves a strange emptiness in him.
\n\n
Amid this position of turmoil Lord Shiva tells Goddess Parvati in Shiv Mahapuran that \" Now for the \' kalyan\' ( emancipation) of mankind I tell you about Rudraksha \" . Rudraksha , is said , to keep our blood pressure in a state of perfect equilibrium thus giving us tranquility and internal peace that helps us in achieving a level of emotional stability . Wearing of Rudraksha also helps us in meditation that is why ancient Rishis used to wear a number of Rudrakshas on their body in order to achieve the state of Samadhi easily and stay in it for a long duration.
\n\n
Rudrakshas help us in achieving a balance and improves our mental faculties .
\n\n
<b>What is the Unique Advantage of Rudraksha ?
\n\n
How Pankaj Khanna\'s Rudraksha\'s different ?</b>
        \n\tPankaj Khanna has been in the trade of Rudrakshas since 1987. The Rudraksha sold by him are collected from deep jungles through the length and breadth of Himalayas . Once collected they are thoroughly checked for originality, quality and efficacy. After this they are stored in accordance with the dicta\'s of the scriptures . Before sending it to the customer Pankaj Khanna himself empowers it with mantras and then in the most pious way it is packed and then dispatched to the customer in a ready to wear form.
\n\n
<b>Who can wear Rudrakshas ?</b>\n\n\t
All human beings can wear a Rudraksha without any restriction of race or gender.
\n\n
<b>After buying the product - What is the process to wear it ?</b>
        \n\n\t
The scared Rudhraksha that you have got is abhimantrit and empowered by Pankaj Khanna, so that it gives maximum results. This is ready to wear or can be kept in your place of worship and should be worn on a Monday morning before 7.30 a.m.
\n\n
To recharge it, you should take it off one week before Mahashivratri. Take a clean bowl and put the Rudraksha in it. Add Pure Desi Ghee in that bowl so that the Rudhraksha is properly immersed in it. Add some sandal wood powder, a bit of turmeric powder (Haldi) in that bowl. Leave it for a week\'s time or more.
\n\n
Then on Mahashivratri day before 7.30 a.m. wash it with Ganga Jal mixed with saffron (kesar) and wear it after chanting the required mantra 108 times. Fasting on Mondays and Mahashivratri day will also be great help and improves the results from a Rudraksha.
    </string>

    <string name="bead_1">
Ek Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to Brahma. Laxmi resides in places where Ek Mukhi Rudraksha is worn after performing the proper rites. This fulfilles desires and cuts down the problems and impediments created by the Government or superiors. It raises a person to a very high level and leadership qualities are astrology it is also used to remove the malefic effects of Sun.
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n
<b>Rs. 4500.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_2">
        <b> \nRs. 501.00 (TWO MUKHI RUDRAKSHA)
            \nRs. 750.00 (TWO MUKHI INDONESIAN RUDRAKSHA)</b>
\n\nDo (2)Mukhi Rudraksha, Two Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the basis of this universe. The benefits that a person derives from the use of this Rudraksha are akin to those derived from AGNI PUJA. In astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Moon Quality : Premium,
\nTwo Mukhi Rudraksha mantra
\nTwo Mukhi (Om Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 600.00
\n\n
Two Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha
\n\n
Rs. 750.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_3">
Teen (3)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB03) <b>(FOR ANY QUERY ON Teen (3)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017)</b> Three Mukhi Rudraksha is a symbol of Brahma, Vishnu and Mahesh. This is considered to be the cause of creation of the three worlds. This curtails the destructive forces within a person and evolves his creativity. This removes the malefic effects of Mars. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Three Mukhi Rudraksha Mantra
\nThree Mukhi (Kali Namah)
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 750.00
\n\n
Three Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha
\nRs. 450.00
\n\n
Three Mukhi Rudraksha Haridwar
\nRs. 300.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_4">
<b>Rs. 200.00 (Four Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 100.00 (Four Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Chaar (4)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB04) <b>(FOR ANY QUERY ON Chaar (4)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017)</b>.Four Mukhi Rudraksha gives results in all the four dimensions of human endeavour; i.e., Dharm, Arth, Kama and Moksha. Wearing this helps in reducing mental problems. In astrology this is said to remove the malefic effects of Mercury. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Four Mukhi (Om Harim Namah)
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\nFour Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 200.00
\n\n
Four Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 100.00
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_5">
        <b>Rs. 101.00 (Five Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 101.00 (Five Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Five (5)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB05) <b>(FOR ANY QUERY ON Five (5)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017)</b> Five Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the form of Mahadeva (SHIVA). Five Mukhi Rudraksha bestows the pleasures of married life. It is said to give wealth, honour and status to the one who wears it. In Astrology it is said to reduce the malefic effects of Jupiter. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\n\n
Five Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 101.00
\n\n
Five Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs.101.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_6">
        <b>Rs. 270.00(Six Mukhi Rudraksha)\n\nRs. 151.00 (Six Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Cheh (6)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB06) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Cheh (6)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Six Mukhi Rudraksha is a form of Kartika and Ganesha. This awakens the sleeping powers of an individual. By wearing this, a person imbibes moral strength, will power and the power of knowledge. This has the complete blessings of Gauri Mata. It gives a person the gift of comprehension. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Venus.
        \n\n
Six Mukhi (Om Harim Humm Namah)\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\n\n
Six Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 270.00
\n\n
Six Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 151.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_7">
        <b>Rs. 1500.00 (Sevan Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese)\nRs. 450.00(Sevan Mukhi Rudraksha Indonesian)
</b>\n\n
        Saat (7) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB07) (FOR ANY QUERY ON seven Mukhi rudrkasha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is said to be dear to Kamdev and is also known by his name. This is also considered to be the form Devi Shakti and Nag Shakti. If it\'s opposite sex\'s affections you are hoping to attract, the Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is exactly what you need. The beads are known to make the wearer irresistible to the opposite sex. This is said to remove the malefic effects of Saturn Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Seven Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Rs. 1500.00 (Seven Mukhi Nepalese Rudraksha)
\n\n
Seven Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha
Rs. 450.00</b>


    </string>
    <string name="bead_8">
<b>Rs.7500.00 (Eight Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese)\nRs. 1500.00 (Eight Mukhi Rudraksha Indonesian)
</b> \n\n
        Aath (8)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB08)(FOR ANY QUERY ON EIGHT MUKHI RUDRAKSHA, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Eight Mukhi Rudraksha is a form of Ganesha. This protects the person from problems related to litigation. Eight Mukhi Rudraksha also saves one from accidents and potent enemies. The wearer does not get agitated and controls the mind. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Rahu. Quality : Premium,
\n\nEight Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Rs. 7500.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_9">
<b>Rs. 9000.00 (Nine Mukhi Rudraksha) Nepalese\nRs. 2001.00 (Nine Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Nau (9) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB09)(FOR ANY QUERY ON Nine Mukhi Rudaksa CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Nine Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be a form of YAMA this has powers of all the nine planets. Nine Mukhi Rudraksha gives the wearer new powers. It is very beneficial in case of unknown diseases This removes the malefic effects of all nine planets and especially KETU Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Nine Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n

The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Rs. 9000.00 (Nine Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese)
        \n\n
Nine Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 2001.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_10">
<b>Rs. 9000.00(TEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA NEPALESE)\nRs. 2001.00(TEN MUKHI INDONESIAN RUDRAKSHA)
 </b>\n\n
        Das(10)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB10) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Das(10)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Ten Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the form of Vishnu and Yama Dev. It is believed that by wearing it you get public respect. Thus, this is very beneficial for leaders, social worker, artists etc. The ten Mukhi Rudraksha is not ruled by any planet but instead controls them all. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Ten Mukhi (Om Harim Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Ten Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese Rs. 9000.00
\n\n
Ten Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 2001.00 </b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_11">
<b>Rs. 12000.00 (ELEVEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA NEPALESE)\nRs. 2500.00 (ELEVEN MUKHI INDONESIAN RUDRAKSHA)</b>\n\n
        Eleven Mukhi Rudraksha (11)MukhRudraksha (code:ARB11) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Gyarah (11)MukhRudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Eleven Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the form of Rudra, i.e., Shiva. As per scriptures one who wears it does not take rebirth. Indra rules this rudraksha thus it gives luxuries and fame to one who wears it. Eleven Mukhi Rudraksha helps in controlling the senses and thus controlling anger. It is one of the most useful Rudraksha, which can bring to the wearer recognition and influence in public life. You need to call +91 9213932017 Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Eleven Mukhi (Om Harim Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>leven Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 12000.00
\n\n
Eleven Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 2500.00 </b>
E
    </string>
    <string name="bead_12">
        <b>
Rs. 18000.00(Twelve Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 3100.00(Twelve Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\
        Baarah (12) MukhiRudraksha (code:ARB12) Twelve Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be a form of the Sun. Lord Vishnu resides in it. If worn on right arm it removes all kinds of fears from the native. It protects from accidents. This gives magnetism to one who wears it regularly. This Rudraksha removes negative forces in the Aura and is a very effective remedy for mental problems. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Twelve Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Twelve Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 18000.00
\n\n
Twelve Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 3100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_13">
        <b>Rs. 21000.00 (Thirteen Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 4500.00 (Thirteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Terah(13) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB13) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Terah(13) Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Thirteen Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be a form of Kamdeva. It improves ones attractiveness for the opposite sex. This is used for Vashikaran. A powerful Rudraksha for those who want to be the center of attraction for the opposite sex and also for people in public life. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Thirteen Mukhi (Om Shrom Namah)
\n\n

The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Thirteen Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 21000.00
\n\n
Thirteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 4500.00 </b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_14">
        <b>
Rs. 120,000.00 (Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 31000.00 (Fourteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Choudah (14) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB14) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Choudah (14) Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha gives strength and enthusiasm to one who wears it regularly. The lord of this Rudraksha is Hanumanji. Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha is said to do wonders in cases where one is unable to have children. In such cases both husband and wife should wear it. This gives the wearer fourteen kinds of knowledge and influence in all walks of life. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
        \n\nFourteen Mukhi (Om Harim Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 120,000.00
\n\n
Fourteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 31000.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_15">
<b>Fifteen Mukhi Rudraksha\n
Rs. 120,000.00</b>
        \n\n
        Fifteen Mukhi Rudraksha Product Code : ARB18 (FOR ANY QUERY ON Fifteen Mukhi Rudraksha, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Ruling planet is Saturn. Fifteen 15 Mukhi Rudraksha is held to sublimate the malefic effects of Saturn, Rahu and Ketu.It improving Intuitive, Abstract and Lateral thinking in addition the wearer finds high energy levels which fight aging and brings better performance in all fields of life. You need to call +91 9213932017
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Fifteen faced Rudraksha is very powerful Rudraksha for those working accomplish Mukti freedom from bondage and Moksa that is Liberation in this physical lifetime. Pashu means individual soul or Jeeva , Pati means Lord and God and Master and Shiva all as one in the same. Pashupati is Lord of Individuals , Lord Siva Lord of animals.
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 120,000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_16">
<b>Sixteen Mukhi Rudraksha
\nRs. 150,000</b>
        \n\n
        Sixteen Mukhi Rudraksha is Mahamrityunjaya form of Lord Shiva. This rudraksha is form of Mahakal. The wearer becomes fearless and gets victory against the most fearsome of diseases and adverse circumstances. A home in which this Rudraksha is kept is free from thefts, fire and accidents. It protects from physical illness due to placement of planets. If one has fear of loss of a loved one or fear of loss of name and fame or loss of faith in oneself or fear of death, then one should wear the Mahamrityunjaya Rudraksha which is 16 mukhi. Mahakal is fearsome form of Lord Shiva which He assumed when Sati burned herself in fire. Even Yama the Lord of Death turns back from the wearer of this rudraksha. Price will be decided on demand
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 150,000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_17">
<b>Seventeen Mukhi Rudraksha
\nRs. 150000.00</b>
        \n\n
        Seventeen Mukhi Rudrasha face Mukhi. (FOR ANY QUERY ON Seventee Mukhi Rudrasha, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Seventeen Mukhi Rudraksha is form of Mata Katyani. Katyani Devi is sixth form of Goddess Durga. It removes obstacles in path and gives immense prosperity. The wearer gets fruits of Dharma, Artha, Kama and Moksha. Wearer lives with immense power and divine magnetism. Gets freedom from diseases, losses, sadness and fears. It gives fulfillment of all desires related to getting a life partner, progeny, good luck and prosperity Represents: Mata Katyani Mantra :- Beeja mantra: Om Kama Kam Katyayani Swaha Wearing mantra: Om Hreem Hoom Hoom Namah. Price will be decided on demand
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n
<b>Rs. 150000.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_18">
<b>EIGHTEEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>
        \n\n
        Eighteen Mukhi Rudraksha (FOR ANY QUERY ON Eighteen Mukhi Rudraksha, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) This rudraksha is form of Goddess earth. The wearer gets health, strength and intelligence. The wearer gets victory in whatever he does, gets immense power and fulfillment of desires. By blessings of Mother earth, the wearer always remains in abundance. It is ideal for people in real-estate and land dealings. If worn by ladies who are prone to abortion, it protects the unborn child and she is able to give birth to a healthy beautiful baby. Represents: Goddess Earth Mantra :- Beeja mantra: Om Hreem Shreem Vasudhaye Swaha Om Hreem Hoom Ektatva rupe Hoom Hreem om\r\nPrice will be decided on demand
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_19">
<b>NINETEEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>\n\n
        Nineteen Mukhi Rudraksha , (FOR ANY QUERY ON Nineteen Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) is form of Lord Narayan the supreme of all Gods. The wearer never has lack of anything in life. It gives immense wealth, success in business , abundance in all spheres and good health . The wearer gets blessings of Vishnu and Goddess Laxmi and is blessed with many virtues , beauty and prosperity. The wearer gets freedom from dreaded diseases , gets perfect life partner . Nineteen Mukhi Rudraksha removes obstacles in job/business/education and removes planetary afflictions. The wearer gets Moksha. It Represents: Lord Narayana and Goddess Laxmi Mantra :- Beeja mantra: Om Vam Vishnave Sheershayane Swaha Wearing mantra: Om Hreem Hoom Namah
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.

    </string>
    <string name="bead_20">
<b>TWENTY MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>\n\n
        Twenty Mukhi Rudraksha This Rudraksha is Brahma swarupa. It has energies of the nine planets, Eight Dikpals (Indra, Varun, Yama, Kuber, Agni, Vayu, Niriti and Ishan) and Tridevas (Brahma , Vishnu , Mahesh). This is highly rare Rudraksha and due to its energies the wearer gets power to achieve almost anything he desires. Twenty Mukhi Rudraksha Represents: Brahma Swarupa Mantra: Beeja mantra: Rudrarupaye Kalpante Namastubhyam Trimurtaye Wearing mantra: Brahmatave Srajaye vishvam Sthitow Palyate punah. Price will be decided on demand
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_21">
    <b>TWENTY ONE MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>\n\n
        Twenty One Mukhi Rudrkahsa. A Rudraksha of Twenty-one face is Lord Shiva. By wearing this remission from the sins of bramahatya could be procured. Moreover wearing it or worshiping it in the house, stabilizes the entire environment and relationship of human to soul. The man hold this Rudraksha is never down on his achievement. All Gods reside within the surrounding of this Rudraksha where it is placed for worship. Wealth and health always remains within the family possesing this rudraksha.The bearer will famous for prosperity and spirituality and always remains in the path of Sanatan Dharma.It is helpful in opening the third eye chakra which governs clairvoyance, sharpened skills, heightened state of awareness etc. Prices will be decided on demand
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_trijuti">
<b>Trijuti Rudraksha</b>\n\n
        Trijuti Rudraksha Code : Trijuti Rudraksha is Trijuti i.e., Bramha,Vishnu and Shiva Roopam. Those who hold or worship this great Rudraksha gets Bramha Gyan.The bearer enjoys superpower in the society. All the benefit of diffrent Mukhi of Rudraksha will be fulfilled by possesing it. Diseases of all sorts in the body internally as well as externally never touches him.
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_ganesh">
<b>
    GANESH RUDRAKSHA
\nRs. 900.00
</b>\n\n
        Ganesh Rudraksha Code : ARB16 (FOR ANY QUERY ON Ganesh Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Ganesha Rudraksha represents Lord Ganesha
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n
<b>Rs. 900.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_gauri">
        <b>Gauri Shankar Rudraksha\n
Rs. 12000.00 </b>\n\n
        Guari Shankar Rudraksha is a Rudraksha that looks as if two rudraksha are joined together one smaller than the other. This is said to fulfill all desires are makes the person satisfied and contented in life. Especially used by people in business who want to earn money in big way and earn it fast.
\n\n
Mantra for Gauri Shankar Rudraksha
\n
Gauri Shankar Rudraksha      (Om Namah Shivai)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\nRs. 12000.00 </b>
    </string>

    <string name="ittr_storage">
        Alcohol (common solvent for most perfumes) causes the perfume to evaporate much faster sometimes unto as much as 10 - 15 times faster. It is important to store ittar in an airtight glass vial in a cool dry place. Ittar has a permanent shelf life and some ittars become stronger and smell better when they are older.
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_uses">
        <b>Uses</b>\n\n
A major difference between synthetic perfumes and ittar is that the oil-based ittar is worn directly on your body. The inside of the wrist, behind the ears, the inside of elbow joints, back of the neck and a few other parts of your anatomy are directly dabbed with ittar. A small drop is enough to be used as a fragrance on the body. A few drops can be added to water and used with aromatic vapour lamps. A few drops of some Attars/Ittars are used with cold drinks, such as milk, to give fragrance.
\n\n
        <b>Culinary uses</b>\n
\n\t• Pan Masala and Gutka is the largest consumer of Indian ittars. The reason for using it is its extraordinary tenacity along with characteristic to withstand with tobacco note. The ittars used are Rose, Kewra, Mehndi, Hina, Shamama, Mitti, Marigold,etc
\n\t• Tobacco is relatively smaller segment for ittar consumption as compared to above industry. The ittars used are mainly kewra and Rose. Along with Pan masala and Gutkha it contributes to more the 75% of ittar consumption.
\n\t• Betel nut is also flvored with ittars such as Kewra and rose.\n
\t• Ittars of Rose and Kewra are used in traditional Indian sweets, for imparting flavor\n
\t• A few drops of some ittars are used with cold drinks, such as milk, to give fragrance.
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_about">
        <b>Ittar</b>\n\n
The word ittar or attar is basically an Arabic word which means scent,this in turn has been derived from the Persian word Atr,meaning fragrance. Attar is a natural perfume oil derived from botanical sources. Most commonly these oils are taken from the botanical material through hydro or steam distillation. Oils can also be expressed by chemical means but generally natural perfumes which qualify as Ittar/Attars are distilled naturally. The oils obtained from the herbs flowers and wood are generally distilled into a wood base such as sandalwood and then aged. The aging period can last from one to ten years depending on the botanicals used and the results desired.
\n
These all-natural perfumes are highly concentrated and therefore are usually offered for sale in small quantities and have traditionally been offered in decorated crystal cut type bottles or small jeweled decanters. Attars/Ittars have been used in the entire Eastern world for thousands of years. These 100% pure and natural perfumes are free of alcohol and chemicals. Natural perfumes are affordable because they are so concentrated that a small bottle will last the user several weeks, if not months. Due to the purity and the nature of oils, there is very little chance of spoilage .
\n
Some of the first lovers of Attars/Ittars were the Mughal nobles of India. Jasmine ittar was the favorite perfume of the Nizams of the Hyderabad state. Traditionally in the Eastern world it was a customary practice of nobility to offer ittar to their guests at the time of their departure. The Attars/Ittars are traditionally given in ornate tiny crystal cut bottles called as itardans. This tradition of giving a scent to one\'s guests continues to this day in many parts of the Eastern world. Among Sufi worshipers the use of Attars/Ittars during meditation circles and dances is quite common.
\n\n
<b>Famous Attars/Ittars List</b>
\n\n\t
• Rose Attar/Ittar (Rosa damascena - Flower)\n\t
• Motia/Jasmin Attar/Ittar (Jasmine sambac - Flower)\n\t
• Mitti Attar/Ittar (Baked earth - Earth from river)\n\t
• Kewda Attar/Ittar (Pandanus odoritissimus - Flower)\n\t
• Saffron Attar/Ittar (Crocus sativa - Stigma)\n\t
• Agarwood/Oud Attar/Ittar (Aquilaria agallocha - Various parts)\n\t
• Gul Hina Attar/Ittar (Lawsonia alba - Flower)\n\t
• Genda/Merigold Attar/Ittar (Tagetes minuta - Flower)\n\t
• Champa Attar/Ittar (Michelia champaca - Flower)\n\t
• Bakul Attar/Ittar (Mimusops elengi - Flower)\n\t
• Blue Lotus Attar/Ittar (Nymphaea caerulea - Flower)\n\t
• Pink Lotus Attar/Ittar (Nelumbo nucifera - Flower)\n\t
• White Lotus Attar/Ittar (Nelumbo nucifera - Flower)\n\t
• Tuberose/Rajniganda Attar/Ittar (Polianthes tuberosa - Flower)\n\t
• White Water Lily Attar/Ittar (Nymphaea ampla - Flower)\n\t
• Zafari Attar/Ittar (Tagetes sp - Flower)\n\t
• Shamana Attar/Ittar (compound of fragrant spices, herbs, woods - Various parts)\n\t
• Amber Attar/Ittar (Pinus Succinifera - ----)\n\t\
• Chameli Attar/Ittar (Jasminum Grandiflorum - Flower)\n\t
• Gulmohar Attar/Ittar (Painciana Regia - Flower)\n\t
• Juhi Attar/Ittar (Jasmine Auriculatum - Flower)\n\t
• Islamic Bakhur Attar/Ittar (Melaleuca Alternifolia - ----)\n\t
• Frangipani Attar/Ittar (Plumeria Ruera - ----)\n\t
• Khus Attar/Ittar (Vetiveria Zizanoides - Roots)\n\t
• Mogra Attar/Ittar (Abelmoschus Moschus - Flower)\n\t
• Loban Attar/Ittar (Styrax Benzoin - Various parts)\n\t
• Nakh Choya Attar/Ittar (Citrus Bigardia - Flower)\n\t
• Davana Attar/Ittar (Artemesia Pallens - Leaves)\n\n
Types of Attars/IttarsAttars/Ittars may be broadly categorized into following types of flavour or ingredients used.
\n\n
<b>Floral Attars/Ittars</b>
\n
Attars/Ittars manufactured from single species of flower are coming under this category. These are :-
\n\t• Gulab ex Rosa damascena or Rosa Edword
\n\t• Kewra ex Pandanus odoratissimus
\n\t• Motia ex Jasminum sambac
\n\t• Gulhina ex lawsonia inermis
\n\t• Chameli ex Jasminum grandiflorum
\n\t• Kadam ex Anthoephalus cadamba
        \n\n
<b>Herbal Attars/Ittars</b>
\n\t
Attars/Ittars manufactured from combination of floral, herbal and spices come under this category.
        \n\t
Hina and its various forms viz., Shamama, Shamam –tul – Amber, Musk Amber and Musk Hina.
\n\n
Attars/Ittars which are neither floral nor herbal also come under this category. Ittar Mitti falls under this category and is produced by distillation of baked earth over base material.
\n\n
Attars/Ittars can also be classified based on their effect on human body such as
\n\t
Warm Attars/Ittars\' Attars/Ittars such as Musk, Amber, Kesar (Saffron), Oud, are used in winters, they increase the bodytemperature.
\n\t
Cool Attars/Ittars\' like Rose, Jasmine, Khus, Kewda, Mogra, are used in summers and are cooling for the body.
\n\n
The Indian ittars in the past was used by the elite, particularly kings and queens. Today it is used in numerous ways
        \n\n
    <b>Health benefits</b>
\n\t• Owing to natural origin it is suitable for all types of skin. It is also useful in treating various skin diseases, various cosmetics, as it helps in improving skin tone and texture.
\n\t• Ittar oils are free from alcohol and any preservatives or chemical additives. They balance the Doshas (Vata, Pitta and Kapha) and promote the energy of the chakras
\n\t• Lemon oil taken internally or sniffed, is good for diabetes, asthma, boils and varicose veins. Three drops of sweet marjoram taken with a little jaggery cures migraine and hangovers. Nausea and vomiting are immediately controlled by petitgren oil.
\n\t• Indian ittar is increasingly being used for aromatherapy these days
\n\t• Jasmine extract is useful in cases of stress, hypertension and treating skin ailments. Inhaling sandalwood oil lessens stress and can stop vomiting. Applying it on the chest and throat cures dry cough.
\n\n<b>Storage:</b>
\n\tIttar has a permanent shelf life and some Attars/Ittars become stronger and smell better when they are older.
\n\n<b>How ittars are made:</b>
\n\tThe art of making these fragrances is a laborious process. There are two types of perfumes. One is extracted from herbs through the process of distillation — it takes 45 days to make them and another one to two years to mature. The second are floral perfumes which are extracted from flowers through hydro/steam distillation. " </string>

    <string name="ittr_1">
<b>Ittar Chandan: Code: AIT 04</b>
\n\n\t        This is made by taking out oil from sandal wood. Its aroma is considered auspicious in all religious ceremonies. It should be used while performing the rites in daily puja. Its fragrance brings peace and tranquility to mind and soul. Beneficial for people suffering from hypertension.
\n\n
        <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_2">
<b>Ittar Motia: Code: AIT 04 </b>
\n\n\t        Attar of Motia attar is used during the worship of Lord Shiva. It is considered to be connected with the aroma of deep forests of lower Himalaya region where Lord Shiva used to move with his followers. Its smell helps in reaching the inner self and is thus used during meditation to get deeper within fast and for lasting peace with one’s own self. People suffering from sleeplessness use it to get rid of their problem and are able to sleep fast. Men are automatically attracted towards women who use this ittar.
            \n\n
        <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_3">
<b>Ittar Gulab: Code: AIT 04  </b>
\n\n\t        Made after crushing gulab Attar (rose) petals, its aroma wards off depressions and brings vibrancy to the user. This gulab Attar is widely used in puja of Lord Ganesha. It also ignites a desire for romance and love. People unable to come to terms with loss of a loved one may carry sadness in their heart for years. When the body (heart or mind) are out of balance, we become more vulnerable to illness. gulab Attar may help gently dissolve blockages and feelings of disappointment and pain.             \n\n
        <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_4">
<b>Ittar Chameli: Code: AIT 04 </b>
\n\n\t        This Chameli Attar is used in headaches and for getting relief from a heavy head feeling which result from excessive noise and general botheration. This Chameli Attar is also used in the worship of Lord Krishna. It is used for giving fragrance to the water with which Lord Krishna is given bath with. In all the rituals connected with Lord Krishna this is extensively used.         <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_5">
<b>Ittar Musk: Code: AIT 04 </b>
\n\n\t        In Hindi it is known as Musk-a-amber. It is derived from the juice of mixture of flowers. Musk ittar is used mostly in tantrik rites. Diyas containing this ittar mixed in oil are lit to attract goddess Laxmi.
        \n\n
        \tThis Musk ittar is also used successfully by males who want to woo the opposite sex. This is said to give an unfair advantage to a male.
        \n\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_6">
<b>Ittar Kewara: Code: AIT 04 </b>
        \n\n
        <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_7">
<b>Ittar Khuskhus: Code: AIT 04 </b>
        \n\n
        <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_8">
<b>Ittar raat ki rani: Code: AIT 04 </b>
        \n\n
        <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="ittr_9">
<b>Ittar Shama: Code: AIT 04 </b>
        \n\n
        <b>Price :Rs.250.00</b>
\n\n\t
<b>
VENUS    :    GULAB (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MARS     :     MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MERCURY    :    CHANDAN (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SUN    :    MOTIA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
JUPITER    :    KEWARA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
MOON    :    RAAT KI RANI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
SATURN    :    CHAMELI (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
RAHU    :    KHUSKHUS (Attars/Ittars)\n\t
KETU    :    SHAMA (Attars/Ittars)\n\t</b>
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_handicrafts">Handicrafts</string>

    <string name="title_activity_jewellery">Jewellery</string>
    <string name="Share">Buy best quality jewellery, spiritual items, gemstones and much much more from Khanna Gems Pvt. Ltd. (Govt Certified).\nGet it now from Google Play.\nClick on the following link to install:\n
    http://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=tech.iosd.gemselections</string>
    <string name="sphtik1">
        <b>Saphatic Shivlinga, Code:  ASA 01.</b>
        \n\nThis is a Yantra, which is used to demolish enemies. If affixed at place of work, it gives complete victory over competitors. Widely used for victory in elections and court cases, it should be hung on a wall facing the entrance on Tuesday after praying to God to finish all enemies
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.900/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik2">
        <b>Saphatic Ganesha, Code:  ASA 02.</b>
        \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Mercury. If worshipped regularly, it improves the strength of nerves and gives the person control over senses. It gives wealth and all liquid assets to the person. In business it is said to increase the flow of cash. It should be affixed on a Wednesday morning between 5.30am and 7.30am.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.900/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik3">
        <b>Saphatic Buddha Head, Code:  ASA 03.</b>
    \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Moon. If worshipped regularly, then it improves the creative powers and gives the person imagination. It helps in weeding out tensions that are not called for. Should be affixed on Monday morning between 5.30 AM and 7.30AM.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.1100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik4">
        <b>Laxmi Paduka, Code:  ASA 04.</b>
    \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Jupiter. If worshipped regularly, it improves the knowledge and status of the person. It gives him influence over his fellow beings and social recognition to the person. Widely worshipped by people in politics and in civil Services. Should be affixed on a Thursday morning between 5.30am and 7.30am.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.900/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik5">
        <b>Saphatic Little Shivlinga, Code:  ASA 05</b>
    \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Rahu. If worshipped regularly one can get the force of luck on his side. It can bring unqualified success in all walks of life. It also gives physical health and attractiveness. Those interested in profits from lotteries, races etc and also in the glamour business like modeling media, etc should worship it.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.200/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik6">
        <b>Saphatic Tortoise, Code:  ASA 06.</b>
    \n\nIf Kuber is pleased and controlled than it bestows abundance of wealth to mankind. The king of Lanka, Ravana had controlled Kuber, which is why his country was called the country of Gold (Sone ki Lanka). Kuber Yantra can be placed both in residential and commercial places. It has to face North and requires regular worship for giving due rewards. The statues of Kuber even guard the building of the Reserve Bank of India in New Delhi.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.900/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik7">
        <b>Saphatic Shri Yantra On Tortoise, Code:  ASA 07.</b>
    \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Mars. If worshipped regularly, it improves will power and gives the person strength, both physical and emotional. It reduces mental tension and controls the temper. Very helpful for those who work in a competitive environment. Should be affixed on Tuesday morning between 5.30 AM and 7.30AM.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.1100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik8">
        <b>Saphatic Shri Yantra, Code:  ASA 08.</b>
    \n\nWhile various gems are used to enhance the benefic power of various planets, yantras are used to control the malefic effect of various planets. The work of Navgrali Yantra, like the work of Navrattan rings and pendants, is to remove the malefic effect of various planets and bring a harmony in their working. This is hung at the entrance of the house or in the place of worship. It brings the vibrations of all the nine planets in harmony.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.901/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik9">
        <b>Saphatic Laxmi ji, Code:  ASA 09.</b>
    \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Rahu. If worshipped regularly it enables a person to control his enemies and defeat them if they try to harm him. It enhances the hidden capabilities in a person. It gives a boost in professional life and makes the person highly successful in rising above competition.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.1100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik10">
        <b>Saphatic Saraswati ji, Code:  ASA 10.</b>
    \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Saturn. If worshipped regularly then it gives the person a strong connection with the omnipotent, thus it enhances the spiritual power. The person gets creative in more than one ways. It improves the social status and gives one authority. People varying from Sadhus to executives worship it for its special benefits.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.1100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik11">
        <b>Saphatic Pendant, Code:  ASA 11.</b>
    \n\nAccording to ancient Bharmana tradition, of all the positive forces of the universe to react in Mahatripurasundri, Shri Yantra is the physical manifestation of this supreme power. This Omnipotent Yantra is used in residential, commercial and religious places with great benefit. Even the powerful Tirupati Balaji Mandir has this Shri Yantra which is worshipped daily with full religious rites
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.200/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik12">
        <b>Saphatic Shank, Code:  ASA 12.</b>
    \n\nUsed to enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of the Sun. If worshipped regularly, it gives success in all walks of life and bestows prosperity in a person\'s life. This improves ones level of concentration and thereby improves the status of the person. It gives public recognition and enhancement of status. It is widely used by businessmen, people in services and those in politics
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.900/- </b>
    </string>
    <string name="sphtik13">
        <b>Saphatic Pyramid,  Code:  ASA 13.</b>
    \n\nThe ancient rishis understood that man by nature is very changeable and will not always live and work as per the rules of Vastu. But by not doing so, he shall be punished by the Vastu Dev. Hence they evolved a Vastu Dosh Nivaran Yantra, which if affixed at the entrance of the house and forgiveness is asked for any mistakes in vastu setting, the native lives happily despite Vastu problems
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.200/-</b>
    </string>

    <string name="japamala1">
        <b>TULSI MALA, Code:  ASS 01.</b>
    \n\nThose who worship Vishnu ’ should wear this mala (Rosary ). It gives serinity and composture,thus helping in concentration. The stem of Tulsi shrub is used for preparing these Malas. These are excellent mosquito repellent and it possesses insecticidal and anti bacterial properties.Thus, its regular use improves the bodily health and composture of the spirit.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.350/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala2">
        <b>CHANDAN MALA, Code:  ASS 02.</b>
    \n\nSandal wood has an aroma which brings spiritual thoughts .It also improves the spiritual and mental power to those who wear it as mala . This mala is also said to remove bad body odor. It should be regularly worn . It is used to chant the name of Lord Vishnu.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.350/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala3">
        <b>LAL CHANDAN MALA, Code:  ASS 03.</b>
    \n\nThis wood improves the concentration of mind .Its paste is applied to cure inflammations and headaches .It is also used as tonic.This mala is used to chant the name of Hanumanji.Itgives one control over senses and energises the body. Highly recommended for students .
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.350/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala4">
        <b>SAPHATIC MALA Code:  ASS 04, Code:  ASA 04.  </b>
    \n\nThe gem sphatic has a quality to be able to remain cooler than the room temperature. This is worn to make a person remain cool under stress. This gem awakens the healing powers and gives extra sensory powers to the wearer. Used for chanting the mantras of Venus (Shukra ).This mala is also said to improve one’s capability to retain what is read.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.601/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala5">
        <b>SAPHATIC RUDRAKSHA MALA, Code:  ASS 05</b>
    \n\nThis is the combination of the powers of Lord Shiva and Lord Vishnu.It should be worn to achieve detachment from the material world and at the same time to control it.People who want to acquire a higher status in life and develop influence on the people they get in touch should wear it. This is also used by people who want higher powers through Reiki ,Pranic healing etc.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.650/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala6">
        <b>VAYAJANTI MALA, Code:  ASS 06.</b>
    \n\nThese are seeds of a plant which are strung as a mala of 108 beads. This was the favorite of Lord Krishna who wore it all the time. The devotees of Krishna wear it to be nearer to him. This mala increases the attractiveness of those who wear it. The wearer also develops a Yogic ability to be calm under extreme provocation. It has to be worn with faith..
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.350/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala7">
        <b>RUDRAKSHA MALA Code:  ASS 07.</b>
    \n\nThis is a rosary which is used to chant the name of Lord Shiva . It gives peace of mind ,controls the blood pressure and also strengthens the mind . In Ayurveda this is used to cure epilepsy .This mala is widely used to awaken the Kundalini Shakti ..
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.501/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala8">
        <b>PEARL MALA , Code:  ASS 08.</b>
    \n\nPearl String Code: ASS 08This string is Natural Fresh Water Pearls. Pearl beads are very good for chanting the name of Vishnu and all his incarnations. It improves the glow in the skin and makes it vibrant. It improves the natural beauty of the wearer. This string improves the imagination, power of expression and the skill of handling people...
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.4100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala9">
        <b>MAGNET MALA ASS 09 Laxmi ji, Code:  ASI 11.</b>
    \n\nThis is a 108 bead string made of Natural Magnets. Wearing it controls the blood pressure - both high and low and improves the general health of the wearer. It improves the magnetism of the person, especially for the opposite sex. It gives the wearer an unfair advantage in rivalry over gaining the admiration of the opposite sex. The legendry Cleopatra was said to wear numerous magnets on her body..
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.1100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala10">
        <b>TIGER EYE MALA, Code:  ASS 10.</b>
    \n\nTiger eye mala is used to chant the name of rahu – i.e., 108 lines in morning before 7.30 A.M OM’ OM’ RAHAVE NAMAH. The regular chant of this name draws out the energy out of one’s enemies. The person is able to rise and show his valour. Though often feared Rahu is capable of giving the top heights to a person..
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.601/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala11">
        <b>NAVRATTAN MALA , Code:  ASS 11.</b>
    \n\nThose who want to get all that the life can hold out to them – want to follow the Hindu philosophy of life – which talks of DHARAM, ARTH, KAM, MOKSHA. Chant Gaytari mantra on this mala and wear it also. This is the mala which brings material wealth and gives one comfort and luxuries comparable to that of INDRA – The king of all Gods.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.6100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala12">
        <b>CORAL MALA, Code:  ASI 14.</b>
    \n\n <b>\"Fortunes favour the Brave\"</b> this is an old saying and its truth can be seen even today around us.  The jap of Mahabali Hanuman on this mala by chanting - BHOOT PRAET NIKET NAHAI AWAWE HANUMAN JO NAM SUNAVE – gives one inner strength – bravery and calm of a brave man.  A brave man is not perturbed by opposition and fighting all odds he is calm and steady.  Ved Vayas the writer of Mahabharata points out that Bhima the great warrior never used to breathe heavily while fighting with his famous Gadha and due to this reason he could finish off his enemies with ease.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.6000/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala13">
        <b>HALDI MALA, Code:  ASS 13.</b>
    \n\nJupiter in the biggest planet and its rays bring prosperity and influence. In astrology the position of Jupiter is considered to be the most important factor in determining whether a person will be able to get what he wants easily or that he will have to struggle through his life.The jap of OM GRAM GREEM GROOM SAH GURUVEH NAMAH improves the strength of Jupiter and thus gives one success with lesser amount of struggle. .
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.600/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala14">
        <b>KAMAL KATTA MALA, Code:  ASS 14.</b>
    \n\nLotus the flower on which Laxmiji sits is considered as on the most auspicious flower in the Hindu mythology. The string made out of lotus seeds is used for Laxmi Jap. The regular Jap of OM! Laxmi Nameh 108 times in a single sitting before 7.30 AM stabilizes and improves the financial position. This brings all round prosperity and influence. People in Ghriasth Ashram (Family people) should do this regularly to get all the material wealth..
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.350/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala15">
        <b>RUDRANI MALA, Code:  ASS 15.</b>
    \n\nThe tiny beads of Rudrani which are rare to find and are wonderful in effect are said to be the female part of the Rudraksha. It is kept in puja rooms along with Rudraksha to get the results of the totality of the Shiva – Parvati jori. Those who keep this jori in their place of worship get all the material pleasures in this birth and salvation after death.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.300/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala16">
        <b>KALA HAKIK, Code:  ASS 16.</b>
    \n\nWearing this mala helps one fight the evil effects of Nazar and Black Magic. A regular Jap of OM! CHAMUNDAI NAMAH. 108 times on this mala in a Single sitting reduces the evil effects of Rahu, Ketu and Shani at the same go. It protects from Tantra and gives the person unique power of synergy with nature.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.1100/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="japamala17">
        <b>PUTRA JEEVA MALA, Code:  ASS 17.</b>
    \n\nThe birth of son in the family gives it strength and continuity. The couples who desire that a son should be born to them should wear it. This not only helps in birth of a male offspring but also helps in giving his long life and strength.
        \n\n<b>Price : Rs.350/-</b>
    </string>

    <string name="stone_ido_head">
        <b>Idols of stone</b> are used in houses and temples to improve the aura and to make the supernatural powers to be on the natives side . These idols are washed with <b>Ganga jal and abhishek</b> has been performed on them , the ceremony which converts a piece of rock into a symbol of God himself .
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol1">
        <b>Lord Shiva, Code: AID 01</b>
        \n\nLord Shiva is considered to be the third Trinity, who destroys all evils. He is the supreme power who controls the Universe. His abode is on Kailash Parvat where he lives with his wife Parvati and their two sons, Ganesh and Kartikya. He is the epitome of simplicity and can be pleased by all kinds of offerings, including leaves and simple flowers. Shivji is especially popular with young girls. It is believed that those who worship him with single-minded devotion are bestowed with good and handsome husbands
        <b>\n\nDimension = 4.75 x 6.5 inch
            \nWeight = 625 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 551/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol2">
        <b>Vanshi Dhari Sri Krishna, Code: AID 02</b>
        \n\nAn incarnation of Lord Vishnu. Among all his incarnations, he is considered to be the most powerful. Said to be the only one who took birth in human form yet possessed all the sixteen qualities described in a perfect human (Solah kala sampurna). He gave a lecture to his dear friend and cousin Arjuna who was bewildered about his duties and about the very concept of life This sermon is a part of the Epic, MAHABHARTA and is called Bhagvatgita or simply Gita. This is the most sacred book of the Hindus. He was said to play flute in his boyhood and its divine music charmed all the natives of Mathura where he was brought up He used the Sudershan Chakra to slay the non-righteousness. In the epic MAHABHARTA he acted as Arjuna\'s charioteer and guided him in slaying people who followed the non-righteous path. Lord Krishna is dear to all Hindus and is worshipped because he can crush evil and bestow one with wealth and happiness.
        <b>\n\nDimension =  6.25 x 2.75 inch
            \nWeight = 345 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 501/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol3">
        <b>Ma Lakshmi ( Godess of Wealth), Code: AID 03</b>
        \n\nThe goddess of wealth and wife of Lord Vishnu, her chariot is an owl. It is believed that wherever the goddess is present, she is accompanied by eight devis namely Asha, Shradha, Dhuti, Shanti, Jai, Shama, Vijit and Sangeet. Laxmiji only appears where there is truth, meditation, charity, justice, fasting etc. If worshipped with purity of soul and devotion she bestows the follower with all sorts of wealth and material comforts.
        <b>\n\nIdol Price : Rs. 150/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol4">
        <b>Badhe Ganesh Ji(Code:AID 04)</b>
        \n\nThe son of Shivji, is considered to be the lord of wealth and intelligence. Ganeshji is worshipped in the beginning of ceremonies or worship to ward off hurdles. He has the head of an elephant denoting an enormously sharp memory, the nose of an elephant denoting his desire to know everything in detail before trying anything new. He has a special love for Laddoos. He shuns wastage, which is denoted by his control over a rodent whom he uses as his vehicle. Ganeshji should be kept essentially at the entrance so that evil spirits do not enter
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 7.5 x 4 inch
            \nWeight = 1 kg. 750 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 751/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol5">
        <b>Badhe Ganesh Ji(Code:AID 04)</b>
        \n\nHe is son of the wind god. He is god of strength and formidable powers at his command. He wards off the influence of evil spirits and other evils and gives internal strength to face adversaries. In Astrology he is considered to be the Lord of Mars .He was a great worshipper of Lord Ram who depended extensively on him to get back his beloved wife Sita. He is also believed to remove all the troubles that his followers face and is always there when needed.
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 3.5 x 2.5 inch
            \nWeight = 190 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 150/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol6">
        <b>Chhote Ganesh Ji(Code:AID 06)</b>
        \n\nThe son of Shivji, is considered to be the lord of wealth and intelligence. Ganeshji is worshipped in the beginning of ceremonies or worship to ward off hurdles. He has the head of an elephant denoting an enormously sharp memory, the nose of an elephant denoting his desire to know everything in detail before trying anything new. He has a special love for Laddoos. He shuns wastage, which is denoted by his control over a rodent whom he uses as his vehicle. Ganeshji should be kept essentially at the entrance so that evil spirits do not enter
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 6.25 x 4 inch
            \nWeight = 825 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 551/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol7">
        <b>Bhagwan Kuber ( The lord of wealth)......(Code:AID 07)</b>
        \n\nAs per Hindu Mythology there is a class of living beings between humans and Gods. These are known as Yakshas. They have small areas of control. Among these, the most famous is Kuber who protects and conserves money. If kept east facing near the place of keeping cash/cheque books etc it regulates the flow of money. It can also be kept in the sitting room to pull in money
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 2.75 x 3 inch
            \nWeight = 530 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 201/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol8">
        <b>Bade Hanuman Ji (Code:AID 08)</b>
        \n\nHe is son of the wind god. He is god of strength and formidable powers at his command. He wards off the influence of evil spirits and other evils and gives internal strength to face adversaries. In Astrology he is considered to be the Lord of Mars .He was a great worshipper of Lord Ram who depended extensively on him to get back his beloved wife Sita. He is also believed to remove all the troubles that his followers face and is always there when needed.
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 11.5 x 4.5 inch
            \nWeight = 1 kg. 590 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs.1250.00/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol9">
        <b>Hanumanji (Code: AID 09)</b>
        \n\n<b>Material : Alwaster</b>
        \n\nHe is son of the wind god. He is god of strength and formidable powers at his command. He wards off the influence of evil spirits and other evils and gives internal strength to face adversaries. In Astrology he is considered to be the Lord of Mars .He was a great worshipper of Lord Ram who depended extensively on him to get back his beloved wife Sita. He is also believed to remove all the troubles that his followers face and is always there when needed.
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 3.5 inch
            \nWeight = 190 grams
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 450/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol10">
        <b>Hanumanji (Code: AID 10)</b>
        \n\n<b>Material : Alwaster</b>
        \n\nHe is son of the wind god. He is god of strength and formidable powers at his command. He wards off the influence of evil spirits and other evils and gives internal strength to face adversaries. In Astrology he is considered to be the Lord of Mars .He was a great worshipper of Lord Ram who depended extensively on him to get back his beloved wife Sita. He is also believed to remove all the troubles that his followers face and is always there when needed.
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 3.5 inch
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 450/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol11">
        <b>STANDING GANESHA (Code:AID 11)</b>
        \n\n<b>Material : Alwaster</b>
        \n\nThe son of Shivji, is considered to be the lord of wealth and intelligence. Ganeshji is worshipped in the beginning of ceremonies or worship to ward off hurdles. He has the head of an elephant denoting an enormously sharp memory, the nose of an elephant denoting his desire to know everything in detail before trying anything new. He has a special love for Laddoos. He shuns wastage, which is denoted by his control over a rodent whom he uses as his vehicle. Ganeshji should be kept essentially at the entrance so that evil spirits do not enter
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 3.5 inch
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 450/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol12">
        <b>Gautam Buddha (Code:AID 12)</b>
        \n\n<b>Material : Alwaster</b>
        \n\nGautam Buddha the founder of the Buddhist religion saw pain and suffering among human beings and founded a path which could give inner peace and develop one’s mind for the higher planes of intelligence. To ultimately transect the cycle of birth and death which gives all pain one should keep the idol of ford Buddha in house.
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 2.5 inch
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 450/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol13">
        <b>Lord Shiva (white stone)(Code: AID 13)</b>
        \n\n<b>Material : Alwaster</b>
        \n\nLord Shiva is considered to be the third Trinity, who destroys all evils. He is the supreme power who controls the Universe. His abode is on Kailash Parvat where he lives with his wife Parvati and their two sons, Ganesh and Kartikya. He is the epitome of simplicity and can be pleased by all kinds of offerings, including leaves and simple flowers. Shivji is especially popular with young girls. It is believed that those who worship him with single-minded devotion are bestowed with good and handsome husbands
        <b>\n\n
            Dimension = 2.5 inch
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 450/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol14">
        <b>LORD MAHAVIRA (Code: AID 14)</b>
        \n\n<b>Material : Alwaster</b>
        \n\n\"If you kill someone, it is yourself you kill.  If you overpower someone, it is yourself you overpower.  If you torment someone, it is yourself you torment. If you harm someone, it is yourself you harm.\" A wise man knows this and so he does not kill, nor does he overpower or torment anyone. This gives him inner peace and his Sanchit Karma is improved.  Keeping the Idol of Lord Mahavira is One\'s place of worship or in the office brings peace of mind and gives a better aura.  Worshipping this Idol daily and taking a row of Ahinsa gives one a unique inner strength freed one from the cycle of life and death.
        <b>\n\nDimension = 2.5 inch
            \nIdol Price : Rs. 450/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stoneidol15">
        <b>BUDHHA HEAD(Code: AID 15)</b>
        \n\n<b>Material : Alwaster</b>
        \n\n\Gautam Buddha the founder of the Buddhist religion saw pain and suffering among human beings and founded a path which could give inner peace and develop one’s mind for the higher planes of intelligence. To ultimately transect the cycle of birth and death which gives all pain one should keep the idol of ford Buddha in house.
        <b>\n\nDimension = 1.5 inch
        \nIdol Price : Rs. 450/-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="kavach_head">We deal in following \'kavach\' products</string>
    <string name="kavach_nazar">
        \tNazar Suraksha Kavach to ward off the evil eye,\n\n\t
Evil eye is a look that is believed by all cultures to be able to cause injury or bad luck on the person at whom it is directed for reasons of envy or dislike.
\n\n\t
The term also refers to the power attributed to certain persons, of inflicting injury or bad luck by such an envious or ill wishing look.
\n\n\t
It usually affects infants and children; they are more vulnerable to evil eye. However, Successful adults are at great risk of harms from evil eye.
\n\n\t
This Nazar Suraksha Kavach is made as per the traditional practice and is available in three forms
\n\tThere are various Yantra\'s in use some are for improving Bhagya others to improve wealth and still others to ward off enemies. Yantra are of three kinds
\n\n\t<b>
Wrist band
        \n\t
Pendent
        \n\t
Wall hanging
        \n\n\t</b>

The use of these protects one from evil eye and bad luck. People of all ages should use it to protect themselves and their families.
\n\tIt safeguards both the health and wealth of the family.
\n\tThe term also refers to the power attributed to certain persons, of inflicting injury or bad luck by such an envious or ill wishing look.
\n\tIt usually affects infants and children; they are more vulnerable to evil eye. However, Successful adults are at great risk of harms from evil eye.
\n\tThis Nazar Suraksha Kavach is made as per the traditional practice and is available in three forms
\n\tWrist band
\n\tPendent
\n\tWall hanging
\n\n\tThe use of these protects one from evil eye and bad luck. People of all ages should use it to protect themselves and their families.
\n\tIt safeguards both the health and wealth of the family.
        \n\n\t<b>Rs. 1100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="kavach_baglamukhi">
        \tThis is all about <b>Baglamukhi Kavach</b>, which is used to demolish enemies. If affixed at place of work, Baglamukhi Kavach gives complete victory over competitors. Widely used for victory in elections and court cases, it should be wear on Tuesday after praying to God to finish all enemies. Shri Baglamukhi Kavach, This is a Kavach, which is used to demolish enemies. it gives complete victory over competitors. Widely used for victory in elections and court cases,
        \n\n\tYantra is the Sanskrit word which means an instrument or a machine. In Tantric texts and Bhramanical Texts it means Visual Mantras or in easy words mantras made in geometrical figures and colours to influence the environment, cosmic forces, spirits around us, the evil eye of our enemies and our own aura and mental makeup. In Hindu and Buddhist mysticism this kind of geometric forms known as Yantra in Hindus and Thangka Paintings or simply Thangka in Buddhist areas is widely seen in Temples, monasteries, Homes and Viharas.
    </string>
    <string name="kavach_durga">
        \t<b>Durga Kavach</b> is a powerful Kavach for attaining desires, to remove difficulties and to conquer enemies. <b>Durga Kavach</b> bestows wealth and property and protects the person from all sorts of dangers.Worship of this Kavach as per Adhayaya 4 sloka 17 of Durga Saptashati removes poverty. It also gives results when used in neck, arm or on body. <b>Durga Kavach</b> is most famous Kavach is very effective. If used with faith it is the most powerful Kavach.\n\n\t
        <b>Durga Kavach</b> is of Shri Durga Ambe Maa. <b>Durga Kavach</b> is worshipped particularly during Navratras and on Ashtami tithi . <b>Durga Kavach</b> is a powerful Kavach for attaining desires, to remove difficulties and to conquer enemies <b>Durga Kavach</b> bestows wealth and property and protects the person from all sorts of dangers. It also gives result when used in neck, arm or on body. Kavach can be defined as visual mantras which have been used since the days of Yajur Veda and Brahminical Text to remove the malefic effects of certain evil forces (Rakshisi Shakti) and to Strengthen the positive forces (Davik Shakti) 
    </string>
    <string name="kavach_hanuman">
        \tFearless and Powerful – Capable of taking on full armies single handily but still devoted and disciplined. This is the nature of Hanuman Kavach It has the powers of the wind god (Pawan putra). Regular puja of Hanuman Kavach fasting on Tuesday and placing a Shri Hanuman Kavach both at the place of worship and in one’s sitting room brings fearless nature, all the evil forces remain at bey and the person is victorious in all his pursuits.
    </string>
    <string name="kavach_shani">
        \tShani Kavach enhance the benefic effects and curtail the malefic effects of Saturn. If worshipped regularly then it gives the person a strong connection with the omnipotent, thus it enhances the spiritual power. The person gets creative in more than one ways. It improves the social status and gives one authority. People varying from Sadhus to executives worship it for its special benefits.
    </string>

    <string name="birthstones_info">
        To find more about the gems mentioned here, <b>please refer to semi-precious gems section in app. :)</b>
    </string>
    <string name="birthstone1">
        Buying Birthstones is a not a very easy task for a layman as the Quality and Originality of Birthstones is something which is difficult to assess for any person who is not a trained Gemologist.
        \n\n
Now let us try to understand these two points in detail:
\n\n
The quality of Gemstones implies the three things:
\n\n
<b>1.\tColour:\t</b> The colour of a Birthstone is the most important factor. More eye pleasing and vibrant the colour of a Gemstone more is its price and simultaneously more is its effect.
\n\n
<b>2.\tClarity\t</b>: The transparency is a very important factor that differentiates between a Stone and a Birthstone. To be effective a Birthstone has to be transparent so that it absorbs the cosmic rays in full strength and transfers it in the body of the wearer. More transparent the Birthstone better is its effect.
\n\n
<b>3.\tLuster:\t</b> Shine and a feeling as if a coloured light is emitting out of a Gemstone is a sign of Quality a Value for a Birthstone. You can feel this Green Light coming out of Emerald (Panna Stone), Red or Pinkish light emitting out of Ruby(Manik Stone), Blue light coming out of Blue Sapphire(Neelam Stone), Yellow light coming out of a Yellow Sapphire(Pukhraj Stone).
\n\n
Originality of Birthstone is even more important because if the Birthstone is not original then all other factors are of nil value.
\n\n
To determine weather a Birthstone is original is not possible for a lay man so the only solution available is to buy from <b>Gem Selections, Janakpuri, New Delhi where you will get a Certificate of Originality from the Gemological Laboratory of Indian Gemological Institute, under the Ministry of Commerce, Govt. of India.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="aries">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tCoral Stone(Moonga)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>Red Onyx
    </string>
    <string name="taurus">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tWhite Sapphire(Safed Pukhraj)\n\tDiamond(Heera)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>\n\t White Quartz \n\tZircon \n\t Aquamarine
    </string>
    <string name="gemini">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tEmerald(Panna Stone)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>\n\t Peridot \n\t Green Amethyst \n\t Green Fluorite \n\t Green Garnet \n\t Green Tourmaline \n\t Green Onyx
    </string>
    <string name="cancer">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tPearl(Moti)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>Moonstone
    </string>
    <string name="leo">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tRuby(Manik)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>\n\tGarnet \n\t Pink Tourmaline \n\t Rose Quartz \n\t Star Ruby
    </string>
    <string name="virgo">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tEmerald(Panna Stone)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>\n\t Peridot \n\t Green Amethyst \n\t Green Fluorite \n\t Green Garnet \n\t Green Tourmaline \n\t Green Onyx
    </string>
    <string name="libra">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tWhite Sapphire(Safed Pukhraj)\n\tDiamond(Heera)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>\n\t White Quartz \n\tZircon \n\t Aquamarine
    </string>
    <string name="scorpio">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tCoral Stone(Moonga)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>Red Onyx
    </string>
    <string name="sagittarious">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tYellow Sapphire(Pukhraj)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>Golden Topaz
    </string>
    <string name="capricorn">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tBlue Sapphire(Neelam)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>\n\t I-olite \n\t BlackStar \n\t Blue Topaz \n\t Smoky Topaz \n\t Turquoise
    </string>
    <string name="aquarious">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tBlue Sapphire(Neelam)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>\n\t I-olite \n\t BlackStar \n\t Blue Topaz \n\t Smoky Topaz \n\t Turquoise
    </string>
    <string name="pisces">
        \n<b>Main Birthstone: </b>\n\tYellow Sapphire(Pukhraj)
        \n\n<b>Substitute Birthstone: </b>Golden Topaz
    </string>
    <string name="semi1">We have the best collection of precious and semi precious gemstones. Select one from the options below to find more about it.</string>

    <string name="handpot1">
        <b>Code : HGL 01</b>
\n\n
A Candle Holder  made of marble with rich colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration or for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  450 grams
\n\n
Height   :  5 "
\n\nBreadth  :  2 "
\n\n
Price  :  Rs 750.00/-
    </string>
    <string name="handpot2">
        <b>Code : HGL 02</b>
\n\n
A flower pot  made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece to own or gift.
\n\n
Weight  :  750  grams
\n\n
Height   :  8 "
\n\n
Breadth  :  4.5 "
\n\n
Price  :  RS 3250.00
    </string>
    <string name="handpot3">
        <b>Code : HGL 03</b>
\n\n
A flower pot made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration and for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  700 grams
\n\n
Height   :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  :  5.5 "
\n\n
Price  :  Rs 3250.00/-
    </string>
    <string name="handpot4">
        <b>Code : HGL 04</b>
\n\n
A flower pot made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration and for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  705 grams
\n\n
Height   :  5 "
\n\n
Breadth  :  4 "
\n\n
Price  :  Rs 3250.00/-
    </string>
    <string name="handpot5">
        <b>Code : HGL 05</b>
\n\n
A Container made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration and for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  300 grams
\n\n
Height   :  4 "
\n\n
Breadth  :  3 "
\n\n
Price  :  1350.00
    </string>
    <string name="handpot6">
        <b>Code : HGL 06</b>
\n\n
A Container made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration and for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  170 grams
\n\n
Height   :  2.5 "
\n\n
Breadth  :  3 "
\n\n
Price  :  Rs 850.00/-
    </string>
    <string name="handpot7">
        <b>Code : HGL 07</b>
\n\n
A Container made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration and for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  850 grams
\n\n
Height   :  5 "
\n\n
Breadth  :  5 "
\n\n
Price  : Rs 1650.00/-
    </string>
    <string name="handpot8">
        <b>Code : HGL 08</b>
\n\n
A Container made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration and for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  700 grams
\n\n
Height   :  4.5 "
\n\n
Breadth  : 4.5 "
\n\n
Price  :  1650.00
    </string>
    <string name="handpot9">
        <b>Code : HGL 09</b>
\n\n
A Container made of marble with rich Colours including 24 k Gold.  A beautiful piece for decoration and for gifting.
\n\n
Weight  :  430 grams
\n\n
Height   :  4 "
\n\n
Breadth  :  4 "
\n\n
Price  :  Rs 1350.00/-
    </string>

    <string name="handclock1">
    <u><b>Marble mobile holder with beautiful watch in it.
(Code - MMW01)</b></u>
\n\n
Marble mobile holder with beautiful watch, with beautiful golden colour hand painting useful for decoration as well as very useful item of keeping mobile or can be used in office for visiting card holder.
\n\n
Rs: 1250/-
\n\n
Weight: 600 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4.5\" x 4\"
    </string>
    <string name="handclock2">
        <u><b>Marble mobile holder with beautiful watch in it.
(Code - MMW02)</b></u>
\n\n
Marble mobile holder with beautiful watch, with beautiful blue and golden colour hand painting useful for decoration as well as very useful item of keeping mobile or can be used in office for visiting card holder.
\n\n
Rs: 1250/-
\n\n
Weight: 600 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4.5\" x 4\"
    </string>
    <string name="handclock3">
        <u><b>Marble decoration item with watch in it.
(Code - MMW03)</b></u>
\n\n
Marble decoration item with beautiful watch in it , with beautiful golden and red colored  hand painting useful for gifting purpose
\n\n
Rs: 1250/-
\n\n
Weight: 830 Grams
\n\n
Size:  7\" x 6\"
    </string>
    <string name="handclock4">
        <u><b>Marble decoration item with watch in it.
(Code - MMW04)
</b></u>\n\n
Marble decoration item with beautiful watch in it , with beautiful golden and red colored  hand painting useful for gifting purpose
\n\n
Rs: 1250/-
\n\n
Weight: 630 Grams
\n\n
Size: 3.5\" x 3\"
    </string>
    <string name="handclock5">
       <u><b> Marble decoration item with watch in it.
(Code - MMW05)</b></u>
\n\n
Marble decoration item with beautiful watch in it , with beautiful golden and red colored  hand painting useful for gifting purpose
\n\n
Rs: 1250/-
\n\n
Weight: 360 Grams
\n\n
Size: 5.5\" x 1.5\"
    </string>

    <string name="handplate1">
        <b>CODE: GPP01</b>
\n\nWhite marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "\n
 Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate2">
        <b>CODE: GPP02</b>
\n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate3">
    <b>CODE: GPP03</b>
\n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate4">
        <b>CODE: GPP04</b>
\n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate5">
        <b>CODE: GPP05</b>
        \n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate6">
        <b>CODE: GPP06</b>
        \n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate7">
        <b>CODE: GPP07</b>
\n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate8">
        <b>CODE: GPP08</b>
        \n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate9">
        <b>CODE: GPP09</b>
        \n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate10">
        <b>CODE: GPP10</b>
        \n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate11">
        <b>CODE: GPP11</b>
        \n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handplate12">
        <b>CODE: GPP12</b>
        \n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of musical instrument.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  250 grams
\n\n
Height  :  7 "
\n\n
Breadth  5 "
\n\n
Price  :  600.00
    </string>

    <string name="handgift1">
        <b>LORD GANESHA PLATE (6" DIA) WITH WOODEN STAND \nCODE: ASG 01.</b>\n\n
This beautiful plate is a perfect showpiece and a item which can be gifted.
\n\n
Rs. 600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift2">
        <b>FRAMED LORD GANESHA PLATE OF MARBLE (9" DIA) \nCODE: ASG 02</b>
\n\n
A work of artisans of Rajasthan this Marble plate of 9 inch diameter with hand painted image of Lord Genesha.  Colors used are rich and permanent and includes an extensive use of 22 k gold in colors. (Framed in exclusive Italian frame is ready to be hanged from walls or placed on a pedestal)
\n\n
Rs. 1800.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift3">
    <b>FRAMED LORD GANESHA PLATE OF MARBLE (6" DIA) \nCODE: ASG 03</b>
\n\n
A work of artisans of Rajasthan this Marble plate of 6 inch diameter with hand painted image of Lord Genesha.  Colors used are rich and permanent and includes an extensive use of 22 k gold in colours. (Framed in exclusive Italian frame is ready to be hanged from walls or placed on a pedestal)
\n\n
Rs. 1100.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift4">
        <b>FRAMED LORD GANESHA PLATE OF MARBLE WITH JALI (9" DIA)  \nCODE: ASG 04.</b>
\n\n
A work of artisans of Rajasthan this exclusive marble plate with beautiful Jali work has a picture of Lord Ganesha painted on it.  The colors used are rich and includes the extensive use of 22 k Gold. (Framed in exclusive Italian frame is ready to be hanged from walls or placed on a pedestal)
        \n\nRs. 2100.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift5">
        <b>FRAMED LORD KRISHNA PLATE OF MARBLE WITH JALI (9" DIA) \nCODE: ASG05.</b>
\n\n
A work of artisans of Rajasthan this exclusive marble plate with beautiful Jali work has a picture of Lord Krishna painted on it.  The colors used are rich and includes the extensive use of 22 k Gold. (Framed in exclusive Italian frame is ready to be hanged from walls or placed on a pedestal)
\n\n
Rs.2100.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift6">
       <b> FRAMED LORD HANUMANJI TILE OF MARBLE 7\"/4\". \nCODE: ASG 06.</b>
\n\n
A work of artisans of Rajasthan than this Marble Tile of 7\"/4\" inch diameter with hand painted image of Lord Hanumanji.  Colors used are rich and permanent and includes an extensive use of 22 k gold in colors. (Framed in exclusive Italian frame is ready to be hanged from walls or placed on a pedestal)
\n\n
Rs. 1100.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift7">
        <b>FRAMED TILE OF LORD KRISHNA AND RADHA OF MARBLE 7\"/4\". \nCODE: ASG 07.</b>
\n\n
A work of artisans of Rajasthan than this Marble Tile of 7\"/4\" inch diameter with hand painted image of Lord Krishna and Radha.  Colors used are rich and permanent and includes an extensive use of 22 k gold in colors. (Framed in exclusive Italian frame is ready to be hanged from walls or placed on a pedestal)
\n\n
Rs. 1100.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift8">
        <b>CODE: ASG 08</b>
\n\n
White marble plate with a beautiful hand painting of Sai Baba.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  : 850 gm.
\n\n
Size       :  9 inch
\n\nRate       :   1200.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift9">
       <b>CODE: ASG 09</b>
\n\n
White marble plate with a beautiful hand painting of Jesus Crist.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight  :  305 gm.
\n\n
Size       :  6 inch
\n\n
Rate       :  600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift10">
        <b>CODE: ASG 10</b>
\n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of Jesus Crist.  The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\n
Weight:290 gm
\n\n
Size:7\"  /  5\"
\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handgift11">
        <b>CODE: ASG 11</b>
\n\n
White marble tile with a beautiful hand painting of Jesus Christ. The Colours used are permanent and include 24 k gold.  It can be hanged from a wall or else can be placed on a table using a stand.
\n\nWeight: 290 gm
\n\n
Size: 7\"  /  5\"
\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>

    <string name="handspi1">
    <b>Undercut Elephant (Code : OSI 01)</b>
\n\n
Elephant (Undercut ) Elephant Indra the King of Devas rode to victories on his famous Elephant “ Eravat ”. In South India where the ancient Indian tradition is still seen intact we see a lot of elephants in temples and in all ceremonies. Elephant is seen as a symbol of prosperity and wealth in Hindu system. When you place a pair of elephants in your house or place of work prosperity in all forms ‘ Aishwariya ’ starts coming to your house. When you gift this to someone it implies that you are wishing all round prosperity and happiness. Having many elephants is a sign of Royalty .

    </string>
    <string name="handspi2">
        <b>Elephant Pair (Soap Stone) \n(Code : OSI 02)
(With Hand Painting)</b>
\n\n
Elephant Pair Indra the King of Devas rode to victories on his famous Elephant \" Eravat \". In South India where the ancient Indian tradition is still seen intact we see a lot of elephants in temples and in all ceremonies. Elephant is seen as a symbol of prosperity and wealth in Hindu system. When you place a pair of elephants in your house or place of work prosperity in all forms \' Aishariya \' starts coming to your house. When you gift this to someone it implies that you are wishing all round prosperity and happiness. Having many elephants is a sign of Royalty . <b>Material Used : Soap Stone with gold painted.</b>
\n\n
<b>Rs. 400.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="handspi3">
        <b>Elephant Pair (Soap Stone) \n(Code : OSI 03)
\n
(With Inlay Work)</b>
\n\n
Elephant Pair Indra the King of Devas rode to victories on his famous Elephant \" Eravat \". In South India where the ancient Indian tradition is still seen intact we see a lot of elephants in temples and in all ceremonies. Elephant is seen as a symbol of prosperity and wealth in Hindu system. When you place a pair of elephants in your house or place of work prosperity in all forms \' Aishariya \' starts coming to your house. When you gift this to someone it implies that you are wishing all round prosperity and happiness. Having many elephants is a sign of Royalty . <b>Soap Stone with inlay work</b>.
\n\n
Rs. 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspi4">
        <b>Pair of Owl (Under Cut) \n(Code : OSI 04)</b>
\n\n
Pair of Owl ( Under Cut ) Pair of Owl is the vehicle \" Wahan \" of Laxmiji the Goddess of wealth. Keeping a pair of Owls in the cash box above the place where valuables of the family are kept also brings goodluck and wealth. Under the Tantrik system if a pair of Owls made of stone is kept wrapped in a red cloth along with sindoor, kewara and saffron hidden under the bed of the head of the family then sudden inflow of wealth starts. <b>Length : 5.5 cm Height : 7 cm Breadth : 4 cm Weight : 140 gm Material Used : Soap Stone</b>
\n\n
<b>Rs. 300</b>
    </string>
    <string name="handspi5">
      <b>Pair of Frog (Under Cut)\n(Code : OSI 05)</b>
\n\n
Pair of Frog ( Undercut ) Pair of Frog Frogs come out of hibernation when rains are expected , rains bring bumper harvests and all round prosperity. Keeping figures of frogs is considered to be auspicious for the householder \" Griasth \". All round wealth and recognition comes quickly to people who keep a pair of frogs in there house or work place. A pair of frogs also makes a wise gift as the person who gets this gift gains tremendously. <b>Length : 10 cm Height : 3 cm Breadth : 6.5 cm Weight : 280 gm Material Used : Soap Stone.</b>
\n\n
<b>Rs. 300.00</b>
    </string>

    <string name="size1">1\"</string>
    <string name="size2">1.3\"</string>
    <string name="size3">2\"</string>
    <string name="size4">2.3\"</string>
    <string name="size5">3\"</string>
    <string name="size6">4\"</string>
    <string name="size7">5\"</string>

    <string name="handspigift1">
    <b>Code: (HGI 01)</b>
\n\n
White marble plate Rajasthani lady in build.  Beautiful hand painting with original and gold colors.  Used for decoration piece.
\n\n
Weight: 850.00gms\n\n
Size: 9 inch\n\n
Rate: 600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift2">
<b>Code: (HGI 02)</b>
\n\n
White marble plate Queen of Rajasthan in build. Beautiful hand painting with original and gold colors. Used for decoration piece.\n\n
Weight: 850.00gms\n\n
Size: 9 inch\n\n
Rate: 600.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift3">
<b>Code: (HGI 03)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile pair of birds in builds.  Beautiful hand painting.  Original colors are used.  Used as a decoration piece.\n\n
        Weight: 290.00gms\n\n
Size: 7\" x 5\"\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift4">
<b>Code: (HGI 04)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile pair of birds in builds.  Beautiful hand painting.  Original colors are used.  Used as a decoration piece.\n\n
Weight: 290.00gms\n\n
Size: 7\" x 5\"\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift5">
<b>Code: (HGI 05)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile pair of birds in builds.  Beautiful hand painting.  Original colors are used.  Used as a decoration piece.\n\n
Weight: 290.00gms\n\n
Size: 7\" x 5\"\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift6">
<b>Code: (HGI 06)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile pair of birds in builds.  Beautiful hand painting.  Original colors are used. Can be Used as a decoration piece or place in stand.\n\n
Weight: 290.00gms\n\n
Size: 7\" x 5\"\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift7">
<b>Code: (HGI 07)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile. Beautiful Rajasthani lady in build.  Beautiful hand painting with original colors.  Can be used as a wall hanging or kept in a stand.\n\n
        Weight: 290.00gms\n\n
Size: 7\" x 5\"\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift8">
<b>Code: (HGI 08)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile colored camel in build. Camel is the symbol of Rajasthan means of transport.  Beautiful hand painting with original colors.  Can be used as a decoration piece or wall hanging.
        \n\n
Weight: 270 gm
\n\n
Size: 6\" x 4\"
\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift9">
<b>Code: (HGI 09)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile symbol of prosperity Elephant is in build.  Beautiful hand painting with original colors.  Can be used as a decoration piece or wall hanging.        \n\n
Weight: 270 gm
\n\n
Size: 6\" x 4\"
\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>
    <string name="handspigift10">
        <b>Code: (HGI 10)</b>
\n\n
White marble tile symbol of power horse is in build.  Beautiful hand painting with original colors.  Can be used as a decoration piece or wall hanging.\n\n
        Weight: 270 gm
\n\n
Size: 6\" x 4\"
\n\n
Rate: 450.00
    </string>

    <string name="handblack1">
    <u><b>Pair Paper weight with beautiful Inlay work
\n
Code : ASG 01</b></u>
\n\n
Black stone paper weight  beautiful inlay work is done.  Very useful in the office or home.  Can be kept anywhere.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-(Pair)
\n\n
Weight: 230 Grams
\n\n
Size:  2\"
    </string>
    <string name="handblack2">
        <u><b>Beautiful Paper holder with Inlay work
\n
Code : ASG 02</b></u>
\n\n
Black stone paper holder beautiful inlay work is done. Very useful in the office or home. Can be kept anywhere.
        \n\n
Rs: 450/-
\n\n
Weight: 850 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4.5\" x 4\"
    </string>
    <string name="handblack3">
        <u><b>Beautiful Pen and Visiting Card Holder with Inlay work
\n
Code : ASG 03</b></u>
\n\n
Black stone pen and card holder beautiful inlay work is done. Very useful in the office or home. Can be kept anywhere.
        \n\n
Rs: 450/-
\n\n
Weight: 430 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 3\"
    </string>
    <string name="handblack4">
        <u><b>Beautiful Pen Holder with Inlay work
\n
Code : ASG 04
</b></u>\n\n
Black stone pen holder beautiful inlay work is done. Very useful in the office or home. Can be kept anywhere.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 400 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 2\"
    </string>
    <string name="handblack5">
       <u><b> Beautiful Visiting Card Holder with Inlay work
\n
Code : ASG 05</b></u>
\n\n
Black stone Visiting card holder beautiful inlay work is done. Very useful in the office or home. Can be kept anywhere.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 225 Grams
\n\n
Size: 4\" x 2\"
    </string>

    <string name="handsoap1">
    <u><b>Pen Stand with Beautiful Inlay work.
\n
Code : TSS 01</b></u>
\n\n
Soap stone pen stand beautiful inlay work is done.  Very useful in the office.  Can be kept in the table.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 400 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 2\"
    </string>
    <string name="handsoap2">
        <u><b>Coaster with Beautiful Inlay work.
\n
Code : TSS 02</b></u>
\n\n
Soap stone pen stand beautiful inlay work is done.  Very useful in the office.  Can be kept in the table.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 600 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 5\"
    </string>
    <string name="handsoap3">
        <u><b>Visiting Card Holder with Beautiful Inlay work.
\n
Code : TSS 03</b></u>
\n\n
Soap stone pen stand beautiful inlay work is done.  Very useful in the office.  Can be kept in the table.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 225 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 2\"
    </string>
    <string name="handsoap4">
        <u><b>Pen Stand and Visiting Card Holder with Inlay work.
\n
Code : TSS 04
</b></u>\n\n
Soap stone pen stand and visiting card holder beautiful inlay work is done.  Very useful in the office.  Can be kept in the table.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 380 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 3\"
    </string>
    <string name="handsoap5">
       <u><b> Paper Holder with Beautiful Inlay work.
\n
Code : TSS 05</b></u>
\n\n
Soap stone paper holder beautiful inlay work is done.  Very useful in the office.  Can be kept in the table.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 850 Grams
\n\n
Size: 4\" x 3\"
    </string>
    <string name="handsoap6">
       <u><b> Pair Paper weight with beautiful Inlay work
\n
Code : TSS 06</b></u>
\n\n
Soap stone paper weight beautiful inlay work is done.  Very useful in the office.  Can be kept in the table.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-(Pair)
\n\n
Weight: 230 Grams
\n\n
Size: 2\"
    </string>

    <string name="handtable1">
    <u><b>PEN STAND WITH LORD GANESHA PAINTING.
\n
(CODE: TTS 01)</b></u>
\n\n
Pen stand made of soap stone with the hand painting of Lord Ganesha on it.
        \n\n
Rs: 180/-(Pair)
\n\n
Weight: 400 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 2\"
    </string>
    <string name="handtable2">
        <u><b>COASTER SET WITH SITTING LORD GANESHA.

(CODE: TTS 02)</b></u>
\n\n
Set of six coasters with hand painting of an elephant on each piece is an exclusive work of art from the artisans of Rajasthan. A picture of sitting lord Ganesha is on the coaster holder keep it on your work or study desk.
            \n\n
Rs: 201/-
\n\n
Weight: 610 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 5\"
    </string>
    <string name="handtable3">
        <u><b>COASTER SET WITH RECLINING LORD GANESHA.
\n
(CODE: TTS 03)</b></u>
\n\n
Set of six coasters with hand painting of an elephant on each piece is an exclusive work of art from the artisans of Rajasthan. A picture of sitting lord Ganesha is on the coaster holder keep it on your work or study desk.
        \n\n
Rs: 201/-
\n\n
Weight: 610 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 5\"
    </string>
    <string name="handtable4">
        <u><b>VISITING CARD HOLDER WITH LORD GANESHA.
\n
(CODE: TTS 04)
</b></u>\n\n
Visiting card holder with hand painting of lord Ganesha on each piece is an exclusive work of art from the artisans of Rajasthan. Can be kept on your work or study desk.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 225 Grams
\n\n
Size:  4\" x 2\"
    </string>
    <string name="handtable5">
       <u><b>VISITING CARD HOLDER WITH LORD GANESHA.
\n
(CODE: TTS 05)</b></u>
\n\n
Visiting card holder with hand painting of lord Ganesha on each piece is an exclusive work of art from the artisans of Rajasthan. Can be kept on your work or study desk.
        \n\n
Rs: 150/-
\n\n
Weight: 225 Grams
\n\n
Size: 4\" x 2\"
    </string>

    <string name="address">
        Shop No. 8 and 11, A-3 DDA MARKET, \n(Near St. Mark\'s School),\n  Janakpuri,\n New Delhi - 110058
        \n\n
        Mobile no.: 09213932017, \n09999136878
    </string>

    <string name="player_error">Error initializing YouTube player: %s</string>
    <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
    <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
    <string name="frag_home_2">More About GemSelections</string>

</resources>
