<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GemSelections</string>
    <string name="tv_payment_1">
        YOU MAY DEPOSIT <b>CHEQUE OR DD </b> ELECTRONIC TRANSFER TO: \n\n
        Khanna Gems Private Limited,\n
        Punjab and Sindh Bank,\n
        <b>A/c No. 08681300000642</b>\n
        <b>IFSC Code: PSIB0000963</b>
    </string>
    <string name="tv_payment_2">
        PAY BY USING\n
        <b>www.paypal.com</b>\n
        to\n
        <b>care@khannagems.com</b>
    </string>
    <string name="tv_payment_3">
        SEND A CHEQUE IN FAVOUR OF\n
        <b>Khanna Gems Private Limited</b>\n\n
        SHOP NO. 8, A-3 DDA MARKET\n
        Janakpuri,\n
        New Delhi - 110058\n
        (Near St. Marks School)
    </string>
    <string name="delivery_message">We deliver anywhere in the World.\n\nThrough the 25 years of its existence Gem Selections has consistently delivered quality and that too at most reasonable prices.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">GemSelections</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="tag_1">(A Unit of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited)</string>
    <string name="tag_2">“Gem Stones is our religion”  \n– Gem Selections</string>

    <string name="about_us">
        Gem Selections came into being on 13th day of January 1987 as a proprietary concern. Its main line of business was buying raw Gem stones from the mines and getting them cut and polished (Lapidary Work) and then supplying these Gems to various Jewellers across India.
        \n\n
        In 1994 it set up a wholesale and retail outlet in JanakPuri,New Delhi and has been handling its marketing operations from there since then. In addition to selling Gemstones it also started manufacturing and selling Diamond and Gem studded Jewellery and Handicrafts made of Semi-Precious and Rough Gems, Rudraksha and other related products.
        \n\n
        In 1997, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited took over Gem Selections with Pankaj Khanna and Anu Khanna as its Directors.
        \n\n
        Judging the value and quality of Gem Stones requires specialised knowledge, training and experience. We at Gem Selections, are dedicated to the highest standards of ethics in helping our customers choose the right Gem Stones which are of the highest quality at the most affordable prices.We regularly update our market information and are always updated about whatever is new in the field of Gem Stones, Diamonds, Jewellery and our other trade products.
        \n\n
        It is the endeavor of Gem Selections to become a benchmark of quality and customer satisfaction in every field of its operations.
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited was incorporated on 20th January,1997 and on 1st April,1997 it took over Gem Selections. Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited deals in retail and wholesale of Gemstones, Diamonds, Jewellery, Handirafts, Rudraksha and other related products. In July 2002 Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited became the back end for all the Gemstones, Rudraksha and Yantra requirements of the Times Internet Limited (www.astrospeak.com). In addition to Times Internet Limited we have been the back end for Gem Stone requirements for www.rediff.com , www.indiainfo.com , www.homeshop18.com , www.sirindia.com .
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited is the only company in India that sells Gemstones with proper Govt. Lab Certificate, be it our brick and mortar shop in Janakpuri or our websites www.khannagems.com and www.gemselections.in. Each and every Gemstone that we sell goes through rigorous testing first at the company level and then we get each and every Gemstone certified by IGI – GTL. Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited assures thequality and transparency in the field of Gemstones.
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited has also been the backend for handicrafts for HHEC since 2007 and Taj Khazana stores in Goa and Mumbai since 2008.
        \n\n
        The guiding principal of the company have been the words of Peter F Drucker “It is the credit the reputation for honest dealings and the dependability of the businessman on which depends his ultimate success or otherwise.” With this ideal the company developed a vast base of 100% satisfied customers not only across the length and breadth of India but also in foreign lands.
        \n\n\n
        <b><i>Vision – To be the global benchmark for quality and be the biggest player in Gemstones, Diamonds and Jewellery Industry.</i></b>
    </string>

    <string name="management_head"><u>MANAGEMENT TEAM</u></string>
    <string name="management_team">
        <b>Pankaj Khanna – Director, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited</b>
        \n\n
        Pankaj Khanna is the founder of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited and has been the Director of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited since its incorporation in 1997. He is a commerce graduate for Sri Venketeshwara College, Delhi University and Life Member of All India Management Association. He completed a Certificate Course in Gemology from Surat Gemology Institute (Regd.) in March 1986. He is a Life Member of Indian Diamond Institute, Surat since 2004 and has been authorized by Indian Institution of Valuers, Pune to use the title of “Chartered Valuer of Jewellery”. He is aLife Member of Consultancy Development Centre, New Delhi
        \n\n
        Pankaj Khanna is also a renowned astrologer and has appeared in approximately 100 episodes of Star Plus program ‘Meri Sehali’ and 60 episodes of E TV program ‘Nari’. Apart from television he has also been widely covered by numerous TV channels including, CNBC, Star News and by national newspapers like The Hindustan Times and The Times of India.
        \n\n

        <b>Anu Khanna – Director, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited</b>
        \n\n
        Anu Khanna has been the Director of Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited since its incorporation in 1997. She is M.Com with specialisation in Finance and Taxation from Delhi University. She has been involved in Gem and Jewellery trade since 1990.
        \n\n
        <b>Anubha Khanna – Jewellery Designer, </b>
        \n\n
        She is an artist and creates unique jewellery designs out of Gemstones and Diamonds for Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited.
        \n\n
        <b>Aaradhya Khanna – Trainee,</b>
        \n\n
        Aaradhya Khanna is a trainee at Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited. He is learning the art and science of handling Gem trade.
        \n\n\n
        <b>A strange love story…</b>
        \n\n
        Pankaj Khanna had a strange fascination for Gemstones and Jewellery. Even as a young child Pankaj Khanna used to visit jewellers and used to see their show – windows from outside. He always wanted to do this trade from the childhood but had no knowledge and family background for the same. He did his graduation from Sri Venketeshwara College, Delhi University and then he went to Surat to formally study Gemology and lived there for one year and did a certificate course in Gemology and wanted to start Gemstones business fulltime. He started his business venture with a meagre amount of Rs.1000 in 13th day of January 1987.
        \n\n
        But simultaneously he had given competitive exams due to social dogmaand was selected in NTPC, a public sector undertaking. He joined NTPC on 5th March 1987.
        \n\n
        But his heart pulled him away and in March 1994 he left the job and ventured full time into his cherished business. He started the business as a supplier to Jewellers and Astrologers across North India.
        \n\n
        In 1997, he founded Khanna Gems Private Limited dealing in retail and wholesale of Gemstones, Diamonds, Jewellery, Handirafts, Rudraksha and yantras.Pankaj Khanna while handling the Gemstones business became a celebrity Astrologer and after the closing the shop in the evening used to work as in-house Astrologer with Taj Mahal Hotel (Taj Group of Hotels), New Delhi and with ITC Maurya Sheraton (Welcome Group), New Delhi. Mr. Khanna has also appeared in approximately 60 episodes of Star Plus program ‘Meri Sehali’ and 60 episodes of E TV program ‘Nari’, where he educated the masses about the various astrological concepts and products. Apart from television he has also been widely covered by numerous TV channels including, CNBC, Star News and by national Newspapers like The Hindustan Times and The Times of India. In 2002
        \n\n
        Even with limited resources and locational disadvantage Pankaj Khanna with his entrepreneurial skills has managed to create Gem Selections as a brand in the field of Gemstones in India.
        \n\n
        He is a Life Member of All India Management Association He is a Life Member of Indian Diamond Institute, Surat since 2004 and has been authorized by Indian Institution of Valuers, Pune to use the title of “Chartered Valuer of Jewellery”. He is a Life Member of Consultancy Development Centre, New Delhi
        \n\n
        In July 2002 Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited became the back end for all the Gemstones, Rudraksha and Yantra requirements of the Times Internet Limited.In addition to Times Internet Limited, Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited has been the back end for Gemstones requirements for www.rediff.com , www.indiainfo.com , www.homeshop18.com , www.sirindia.com . Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited is the only company in India that sells Gemstones with proper Govt. Lab Certificate, be it our brick and mortar shop in Janakpuri or our websites www.khannagems.com and www.gemselections.in. Each and every Gemstone that we sell goes through rigorous testing first at the company level and then we get each and every Gemstone certified by IGI – GTL. Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited is the benchmark for quality and transparency in the field of Gemstones.
        \n\n
        Khanna Gems Pvt. Limited has also been the backend for handicrafts for HHEC since 2007 and Taj Khazana stores in Goa and Mumbai since 2008.
    </string>
    <string name="_pankaj">
        Sh. Pankaj Khanna who is a renowned Astrologer is also a Certified Gemologist and Jewellery Valuer. He has strived hard all his life so that people are able to get: \n
        \n\t\t 1. Original Gemstones.
        \n\t\t 2. Gemstones with a high efficacy.
        \n\t\t 3. Gemstones that are property abhimantrit and charged.
        \n\t\t 4. Gemstones that come with full disclosure as to any treatment or enhancement.
    </string>
    <string name="_khanna_gems">
        <b>Khanna Gems Private Limited</b> Started its Operations on 1st – April – 1997 by taking over the business of Gem Selections a 10 years old firm.
        \n\n
        The Core Business of Khanna Gems Private Limited it to procure rough Gemstones from mines and then cut and polish them.
        \n\n
        All varieties of Precious and Semi-Precious Gemstones are dealt with at Khanna Gems Private Limite.
        \n\n
        The Gemstones are checked for purity, efficacy and superior cutting and then send to Govt. Lab of Gem and Jewellery Export Promotion council for certification.
        \n\n
        The entire inventory at Khanna Gems Private Limited is Govt. Lab Certified.
        \n\n
        The Khanna Gems Private Limited is known for quality and originality of its Gemstones and dependability of it dealings.
        \n\n
        <b><i>Our Motto: Original Gemstones always and every time.</i></b>
    </string>
    <string name="frag_home_1">We also make rings and pendants</string>
    <string name="copyright">© KHANNA GEMS PVT. LTD.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_rudraksha">Rudraksha</string>

    <string name="_rud_mantra">
        One Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Two Mukhi \t<b>(Om Namah)</b>\n\n
        Three Mukhi \t<b>(Kali Namah)</b>\n\n
        Four Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Five Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Six Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Seven Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Eight Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Nine Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Ten Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Eleven Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Twelve Mukhi \t<b>(Om Humm Namah)</b>\n\n
        Thirteen Mukhi \t<b>(Om Shrom Namah)</b>\n\n
        Fourteen Mukhi \t<b>(Om Harim Namah)</b>\n\n
        Gauri Shankar \t<b>(Om Namah Shivai)</b>\n\n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="_rud_how_to_wear">
        The scared Rudhraksha that you have got is abhimantrit and empowered by Pankaj Khanna, so that it gives maximum results. This is ready to wear or can be kept in your place of worship and should be worn on a Monday morning before 7.30 a.m.
        \n\n
        To recharge it, you should take it off one week before Mahashivratri. Take a clean bowl and put the Rudraksha in it. Add Pure Desi Ghee in that bowl so that the Rudhraksha is properly immersed in it. Add some sandal wood powder, a bit of turmeric powder (Haldi) in that bowl. Leave it for a week’s time or more.
        \n\n
        Then on Mahashivratri day before 7.30 a.m. wash it with Ganga Jal mixed with saffron (kesar) and wear it after chanting the required mantra 108 times. Fasting on Mondays and Mahashivratri day will also be great help and improves the results from a Rudraksha.
    </string>
    <string name="_rud_auth">
        The Mystic bead Rudhraksha is highly sacred to the Hindus of all castes / sects and regions. But as some of the Rudhraksha are very costly so some people out of greed try to tamper with the Rudhraksha so as to make them like a more costly member of the family.
        \n\n
        <b>Now, the question before the buyer is how he should check the authenticity of the Rudhraksha.</b>
        \n\n\n
        <b>1. EYE TEST:</b> Look at the bead all the mukhas / faces should look like joined lips and the partitions where the line is visible should be clear and look natural.
        \n\n
        <b>2. EYE GLASS:</b> Sometimes Rudhraksha are faked by removing the thorn like parts from one piece and then sticking it to another. This can be judged by a close examination by a 10x Lens.
        \n\n
        <b>3. WATER TEST:</b> Put the Rudhraksha in boiling water and let it remain there for 20 – 30 minutes. If some faces are tempered with them they shall come off as the glue – fevicol or the like will come off.
        \n\n
        <b>4. SCIENTIFIC TEST:</b> A botanical laboratory or a botanist can test a Rudhraksha and testify its originality. So, if in doubt take the Rudhraksha to a Botanical laboratory and know the facts.
    </string>
    <string name="_rud_faqs">
        <b>1. How can, this mystic power named Rudhraksha, be used by mankind for maximum benefit?</b>
        \n\n
        \tRudhraksha can either be worn in neck or it can be at a sacred place in house i.e., in the puja room or in front of God’s / Goddess’s idol or picture.
        \n\n
        <b>2. Should Rudhraksha be worn all the time?</b>
        \n\n
        \tIf one chooses to wear a Rudhraksha then he/she should wear it all the day and take off before going to bed. Then it should be worn again after the morning puja / prayers.
        \n\n
        <b>3. Can one eat non-vegetarian food and take alcohol if one is wearing Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \tThough taking non-vegetarian food and alcohol is not recommended to keep the Sanchit Karma pure but the Shiva sect of Hindu religion of which Rudhraksha is a symbol – does not prohibit it. So, one can take non-vegetarian food and take alcohol while wearing Rudhraksha.
        \n\n
        <b>4. What is the greatest use of Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \tRudhraksha beads regulate the blood pressure thus helping in controlling the thought process. This helps in Meditations which is the ultimate tool to realize the power of the inner self.
        \n\n
        <b>5. Does wearing Rudhraksha bring results?</b>
        \n\n
        \tThough one of the most sacred possessions of a Hindu – Rudhraksha does not lead to instant results but if worn over a period of time with complete faith and the required mantras are chanted regularly then the results promised by the Mahashiv Purana are surely achieved – this is what the sages say.
        \n\n
        <b>6. What is the cost of one Mukhi Round Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \tOne Mukhi Round Rudhraksha, which is said to have extraordinary powers is often heard of but such a piece is not seen in trade – I have never come across such a piece which is original, though I am trading in them since 1987.
        \n\n
        <b>7. How else can we get the benefits of Rudhraksha?</b>
        \n\n
        \t(1) Rudhraksha can be kept in the place of worship.
        \n
        \t(2) One can dip seven beads of five Mukhi Rudhraksha in a glass of water and drink the water daily in the morning. This improves the blood circulation, gives one better concentration and the general nervous system in improved. The Rudhraksha beads have to be changed after every seven days.
    </string>

    <string name="_bracelet">
        <b>Rudraksha Bracelet</b>
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 1100.00</b>
        \n\n
        \tThe birth of son in the family gives it strength and continuity. The couples who desire that a son should be born to them should wear it. This not only helps in birth of a male offspring but also helps in giving his long life and strength.
        \n\n\n
        <b>\tThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
        Rs. 1100.00
    </string>
    <string name="_bracelet_two">
        <b>Two Mukhi Rudraksha Bracelet</b>
        \n\n
        \tThis fulfills desires and cuts down the problems and impediments created by the Government or superiors. It raises a person to a very high level and leadership qualities are developed by its constant use
        \n\n\n
        <b>\tThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
Rs.     <b>Rs. 1000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_bracelet_three">
        <b>Three Mukhi Rudraksha Bracelet</b>
        \n\n
        \tThis fulfills desires and cuts down the problems and impediments created by the Government or superiors. It raises a person to a very high level and leadership qualities are developed by its constant use.
        \n\n\n
        \t<b>The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
       <b>Rs. 1000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_bracelet_four">
        <b>Rudraksha Pearl Combination</b>
        \n\n
        \tThis string is Natural Fresh Water Pearls. Pearl beads are very good for chanting the name of Vishnu and all his incarnations. It improves the glow in the skin and makes it vibrant. It improves the natural beauty of the wearer. This string improves the imagination, power of expression and the skill of handling people.
        \n\n
        \tThis is a rosary which is used to chant the name of Lord Shiva . It gives peace of mind ,controls the blood pressure and also strengthens the mind . In Ayurveda this is used to cure epilepsy .This mala is widely used to awaken the Kundalini Shakti .
        \n\n
        <b>\tThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        </b>\n\n
        <b>Rs. 501.00 </b>
    </string>

    <string name="_mala1">TWO MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 41550.00</string>
    <string name="_mala2">
        Two Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the basis of this universe. The benefits that a person derives from the use of this Rudraksha are akin to those derived from AGNI PUJA. In astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Moon Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        Two Mukhi Rudraksha mantra
        \n\n
        Two Mukhi (Om Namah)
        \n\n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 41550.00
    </string>
    <string name="_mala3">THREE MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 21000.00</string>
    <string name="_mala4">
        Three Mukhi Rudraksha mala is a symbol of Brahma, Vishnu and Mahesh. This is considered to be the cause of creation of the three worlds. This curtails the destructive forces within a person and evolves his creativity. This removes the malefic effects of Mars. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 21000.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala5">FOUR MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 2650.00</string>
    <string name="_mala6">
        Four Mukhi Rudraksha Mala gives results in all the four dimensions of human endeavour; i.e., Dharm, Arth, Kama and Moksha. Wearing this helps in reducing mental problems. In astrology this is said to remove the malefic effects of Mercury. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 2650.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala7">FIVE MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 600.00</string>
    <string name="_mala8">
        Paach Mukhi Rudraksha Mala (five mukhi ) This is a rosary which is used to chant the name of Lord Shiva . It gives peace of mind ,controls the blood pressure and also strengthens the mind . In Ayurveda this is used to cure epilepsy .This mala is widely used to awaken the Kundalini Shakti .
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala9">SIX MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 2650.00</string>
    <string name="_mala10">
        Six Mukhi Rudraksha Mala is a form of Kartika and Ganesha. This awakens the sleeping powers of an individual. By wearing this, a person imbibes moral strength, will power and the power of knowledge. This has the complete blessings of Gauri Mata. It gives a person the gift of comprehension. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Venus. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 2650.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala11">SEVEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 10000.00</string>
    <string name="_mala12">
        Seven Mukhi Rudraksha Mala is said to be dear to Kamdev and is also known by his name. This is also considered to be the form Devi Shakti and Nag Shakti. If it\'s a woman\'s affections you are hoping to attract, the Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is exactly what you need. The beads are known to make the wearer irresistible to the female of the species. This is said to remove the malefic effects of Saturn Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        Rs. 10000.00
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>
    <string name="_mala13">EIGHT MUKHI RUDRAKSHA MALA\n\nRs. 8300.00</string>
    <string name="_mala14">
        Eight Mukhi Rudraksha Mala is a form of Ganesha. This protects the person from problems related to litigation. This also saves one from accidents and potent enemies. The wearer does not get agitated and controls the mind. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Rahu. Quality : Premium,
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        OM NAMAH SHIVAY
    </string>

    <string name="_yugal1">Aakarshan Vriddhi Yantra</string>
    <string name="_yugal2">
    Aakarshan Vriddhi Yantra. (AVY08) Cleopatra was known to wear magnets on her body and that helped her to attract the opposite sex. Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is manifestation of Kamdev and pearl is the Gem of Beauty these there in. Combination can gives you an unfore advantage in attracting the opposite sex and retaining it. Men and Women of all age groups can use it. Advantageously
        \n\nThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 6000.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal3">Laxmi Vardhak Yugal\n\nRs. 2100.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal4">
    Laxmi Vardhak Yugal. (LVY02) Rudraksha Combination for Wealth (Laxmi Vardhak Yugal) : Six Mukhi Rudraksha has the powers of Venus it gives wealth. Laxmiji resides where Six Mukhi is kept. In combination with Four Mukhi Rudraksha which is the manifestation of Genesha and Emerald which brings all kinds of wealth and makes it stable. If this combination is worn regularly and Laxmi Strota is recited daily then all wants of the person are automatically fulfilled and he is never seen in a state of dissatisfaction.
    \n\nThe Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    \n\n
    <b>Rs. 2100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal5">Raktachap Niyantran Raj Yog Yugal</string>
    <string name="_yugal6">
        Raktachap Niyantran tatha Rajya such Yugal. (RNT06) Sun is the regulator of heart and blood stream in combination with Rudraksha it is said to give special efforts. It also help in giving better status in service and gives the support of the government and seniors. Rudraksha Mala, 7.25 Rati Ruby Surya lockets made of 92.5% Pure Silver with Surya Mantra Engraved on it.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 3100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal7">Sarve Manokamana Prapti Yugal \n\nRs. 2100.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal8">
        Sarve Manokamana Prapti Yugal. (SMY09) Life is short and the desires of mankind are multiple. The planet Jupiter is said to give earthly pleasures and also salvation after death. Sarva Mano – Kamna Prapti Yugal empowers Jupiter and gives all that a man desires in life. It contains 3.25 rt Golden Topaz made in silver with Guru Mantra inscribed on it strung in a thread with two beads of the mighty Five Mukhi Rudraksha. It should be regularly worn and the mantra of Jupiter ‘Om ! Gram Greem Groom Sah Guruve Namah’ should be regularly chanted to strengthen Jupiter and for fulfilment of all desires.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 2100.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="_yugal9">Shatru Nashak Yugal \n\nRs.1550.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal10">
        Shatru Nashak Yugal. (SNY03) Rudraksha Combination to Win Over Enemies (Shatru Nashak Yugal): All successful people have to face enemies created by envy. Enemies not only try to harm you by various means but also steel your peace of mind. Various Vedic prayers and Tantric rituals are available for steeling a victory over ones enemies. Shatru Nashak Rudraksha Yugal is aimed at puncturing the power base of the people having ill feelings or enmity towards you. It weakens there resolve and creates problems for them so that instead of putting there mind on creating problems for you they get busy fighting for there own survival.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 1550.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="_yugal11">Sukhi Bhav Yugal\n\nRs. 2100.00</string>
    <string name="_yugal12">
        Sukhi Bhav Yugal. (SBY05) Rudraksha Combination for Betterment of Married Life / Love (Sukhi Bhav Yugal) : All wealth, fame, success and achievements seem useless for a person who does not get love in life, instead of happiness there is a constant state of depression. To overcome these problems one should wear this Yugal. If one wears it regularly and chants Gayatri Mantra he/she gets love from the cherished members of opposite sex giving a sense of fulfilment.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 2100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal13">Vidya Vardhak Yugal\n\nRs. 5100.00 </string>
    <string name="_yugal14">
        Vidya Vardhak Yugal. (VVY01) Rudraksha Combination for Education (Vidya Vardhak Yugal) This Rudraksha combination (Yugal) improves the level of concentration, retentive power and restrains the mind from being deverted towards Maya created by the various Rajasik and Tamsik powers (shakties) of nature. The results that the students get by wearing this combination are simply amazing. There retentive power and intelligence level improves leading to better grades.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 5100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal15">Vijaye Bhav Yugal\n\nRs. 11000.00 </string>
    <string name="_yugal16">
        Vijaye Bhav Yugal. (VBY04) Rudraksha Combination to get Professional Rise (Vijaye Bhav Yugal) Nothing succeeds like success is a truth known to all of us but our efforts are not always rewarded and we all often feel that there are certain cosmic powers which must support our efforts in order to give us a lasting success. Vijaye Bhav Yugal helps in getting support of these powers. If this Yugal is constantly worn and the mantra ‘Om Namah Shivae’ is regularly chanted then the efforts of the person are invariably crowned with success.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 11000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="_yugal17">Vyapar Vridhi Karja Mukti Yugal\n\nRs. 5100.00 </string>
    <string name="_yugal18">
        Vyapar Vridhi Karja Mukti Yugal. (VVK07) Emerals ie, Morkat mani or Panna is the Gem of lord Ganesha this Gem gives enhancement of wealth and success in Business ventures in combination with the Rudraksha of Budh the Four Mukhi Rudraksha it gives Instant results. It is a must for people who want to rice in Business and make their Enjoining or future venture a Success. Two Four Mukhi Rudraksha With 7.25 rati Emeralds in 92.5% Pure Silver Yantra With Budh Mantra Engraved on in.
        \n\n
        The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
        \n\n
        <b>Rs. 5100.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="tag_3">\" The Message \n\" Rudraksha – \nFrom Lord Shiva with Love</string>
    <string name="_rud_home">
    <b>Why Rudraksha - At the First Stage ?</b>\n\n\t
The human life is full of pain both on the physical as well as emotional level. Our ancient Rishis tried to search for cures for all ailments that effect us . These cures were in the form of Auyerveda , religion etc . But even with a healthy body and complete devotion to God man does not feel happy and to large extent all his efforts after fulfillment of basic bread and butter needs are aimed at searching for that happiness. He wanders in search of this happiness in Disco Thiks and nightclubs or else in Rishikesh or temples ………….. he tries to earn extraordinary money, be a leader but all this leaves a strange emptiness in him.
\n\n
Amid this position of turmoil Lord Shiva tells Goddess Parvati in Shiv Mahapuran that \" Now for the \' kalyan\' ( emancipation) of mankind I tell you about Rudraksha \" . Rudraksha , is said , to keep our blood pressure in a state of perfect equilibrium thus giving us tranquility and internal peace that helps us in achieving a level of emotional stability . Wearing of Rudraksha also helps us in meditation that is why ancient Rishis used to wear a number of Rudrakshas on their body in order to achieve the state of Samadhi easily and stay in it for a long duration.
\n\n
Rudrakshas help us in achieving a balance and improves our mental faculties .
\n\n
<b>What is the Unique Advantage of Rudraksha ?
\n\n
How Pankaj Khanna\'s Rudraksha\'s different ?</b>
        \n\tPankaj Khanna has been in the trade of Rudrakshas since 1987. The Rudraksha sold by him are collected from deep jungles through the length and breadth of Himalayas . Once collected they are thoroughly checked for originality, quality and efficacy. After this they are stored in accordance with the dicta\'s of the scriptures . Before sending it to the customer Pankaj Khanna himself empowers it with mantras and then in the most pious way it is packed and then dispatched to the customer in a ready to wear form.
\n\n
<b>Who can wear Rudrakshas ?</b>\n\n\t
All human beings can wear a Rudraksha without any restriction of race or gender.
\n\n
<b>After buying the product - What is the process to wear it ?</b>
        \n\n\t
The scared Rudhraksha that you have got is abhimantrit and empowered by Pankaj Khanna, so that it gives maximum results. This is ready to wear or can be kept in your place of worship and should be worn on a Monday morning before 7.30 a.m.
\n\n
To recharge it, you should take it off one week before Mahashivratri. Take a clean bowl and put the Rudraksha in it. Add Pure Desi Ghee in that bowl so that the Rudhraksha is properly immersed in it. Add some sandal wood powder, a bit of turmeric powder (Haldi) in that bowl. Leave it for a week\'s time or more.
\n\n
Then on Mahashivratri day before 7.30 a.m. wash it with Ganga Jal mixed with saffron (kesar) and wear it after chanting the required mantra 108 times. Fasting on Mondays and Mahashivratri day will also be great help and improves the results from a Rudraksha.
    </string>

    <string name="bead_1">
Ek Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to Brahma. Laxmi resides in places where Ek Mukhi Rudraksha is worn after performing the proper rites. This fulfilles desires and cuts down the problems and impediments created by the Government or superiors. It raises a person to a very high level and leadership qualities are astrology it is also used to remove the malefic effects of Sun.
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n
<b>Rs. 4500.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_2">
        <b> \nRs. 501.00 (TWO MUKHI RUDRAKSHA)
            \nRs. 750.00 (TWO MUKHI INDONESIAN RUDRAKSHA)</b>
\n\nDo (2)Mukhi Rudraksha, Two Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the basis of this universe. The benefits that a person derives from the use of this Rudraksha are akin to those derived from AGNI PUJA. In astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Moon Quality : Premium,
\nTwo Mukhi Rudraksha mantra
\nTwo Mukhi (Om Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 600.00
\n\n
Two Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha
\n\n
Rs. 750.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_3">
Teen (3)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB03) <b>(FOR ANY QUERY ON Teen (3)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017)</b> Three Mukhi Rudraksha is a symbol of Brahma, Vishnu and Mahesh. This is considered to be the cause of creation of the three worlds. This curtails the destructive forces within a person and evolves his creativity. This removes the malefic effects of Mars. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Three Mukhi Rudraksha Mantra
\nThree Mukhi (Kali Namah)
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 750.00
\n\n
Three Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha
\nRs. 450.00
\n\n
Three Mukhi Rudraksha Haridwar
\nRs. 300.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_4">
<b>Rs. 200.00 (Four Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 100.00 (Four Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Chaar (4)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB04) <b>(FOR ANY QUERY ON Chaar (4)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017)</b>.Four Mukhi Rudraksha gives results in all the four dimensions of human endeavour; i.e., Dharm, Arth, Kama and Moksha. Wearing this helps in reducing mental problems. In astrology this is said to remove the malefic effects of Mercury. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Four Mukhi (Om Harim Namah)
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\nFour Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 200.00
\n\n
Four Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 100.00
</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_5">
        <b>Rs. 101.00 (Five Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 101.00 (Five Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Five (5)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB05) <b>(FOR ANY QUERY ON Five (5)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017)</b> Five Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the form of Mahadeva (SHIVA). Five Mukhi Rudraksha bestows the pleasures of married life. It is said to give wealth, honour and status to the one who wears it. In Astrology it is said to reduce the malefic effects of Jupiter. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\n\n
Five Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 101.00
\n\n
Five Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs.101.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_6">
        <b>Rs. 270.00(Six Mukhi Rudraksha)\n\nRs. 151.00 (Six Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Cheh (6)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB06) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Cheh (6)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Six Mukhi Rudraksha is a form of Kartika and Ganesha. This awakens the sleeping powers of an individual. By wearing this, a person imbibes moral strength, will power and the power of knowledge. This has the complete blessings of Gauri Mata. It gives a person the gift of comprehension. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Venus.
        \n\n
Six Mukhi (Om Harim Humm Namah)\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\n\n
Six Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 270.00
\n\n
Six Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 151.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_7">
        <b>Rs. 1500.00 (Sevan Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese)\nRs. 450.00(Sevan Mukhi Rudraksha Indonesian)
</b>\n\n
        Saat (7) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB07) (FOR ANY QUERY ON seven Mukhi rudrkasha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is said to be dear to Kamdev and is also known by his name. This is also considered to be the form Devi Shakti and Nag Shakti. If it\'s opposite sex\'s affections you are hoping to attract, the Seven Mukhi Rudraksha is exactly what you need. The beads are known to make the wearer irresistible to the opposite sex. This is said to remove the malefic effects of Saturn Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Seven Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Rs. 1500.00 (Seven Mukhi Nepalese Rudraksha)
\n\n
Seven Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha
Rs. 450.00</b>


    </string>
    <string name="bead_8">
<b>Rs.7500.00 (Eight Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese)\nRs. 1500.00 (Eight Mukhi Rudraksha Indonesian)
</b> \n\n
        Aath (8)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB08)(FOR ANY QUERY ON EIGHT MUKHI RUDRAKSHA, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Eight Mukhi Rudraksha is a form of Ganesha. This protects the person from problems related to litigation. Eight Mukhi Rudraksha also saves one from accidents and potent enemies. The wearer does not get agitated and controls the mind. In Astrology it is said to remove the malefic effects of Rahu. Quality : Premium,
\n\nEight Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Rs. 7500.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_9">
<b>Rs. 9000.00 (Nine Mukhi Rudraksha) Nepalese\nRs. 2001.00 (Nine Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Nau (9) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB09)(FOR ANY QUERY ON Nine Mukhi Rudaksa CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Nine Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be a form of YAMA this has powers of all the nine planets. Nine Mukhi Rudraksha gives the wearer new powers. It is very beneficial in case of unknown diseases This removes the malefic effects of all nine planets and especially KETU Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Nine Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n

The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Rs. 9000.00 (Nine Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese)
        \n\n
Nine Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 2001.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_10">
<b>Rs. 9000.00(TEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA NEPALESE)\nRs. 2001.00(TEN MUKHI INDONESIAN RUDRAKSHA)
 </b>\n\n
        Das(10)Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB10) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Das(10)Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Ten Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the form of Vishnu and Yama Dev. It is believed that by wearing it you get public respect. Thus, this is very beneficial for leaders, social worker, artists etc. The ten Mukhi Rudraksha is not ruled by any planet but instead controls them all. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Ten Mukhi (Om Harim Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Ten Mukhi Rudraksha Nepalese Rs. 9000.00
\n\n
Ten Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 2001.00 </b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_11">
<b>Rs. 12000.00 (ELEVEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA NEPALESE)\nRs. 2500.00 (ELEVEN MUKHI INDONESIAN RUDRAKSHA)</b>\n\n
        Eleven Mukhi Rudraksha (11)MukhRudraksha (code:ARB11) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Gyarah (11)MukhRudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Eleven Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be the form of Rudra, i.e., Shiva. As per scriptures one who wears it does not take rebirth. Indra rules this rudraksha thus it gives luxuries and fame to one who wears it. Eleven Mukhi Rudraksha helps in controlling the senses and thus controlling anger. It is one of the most useful Rudraksha, which can bring to the wearer recognition and influence in public life. You need to call +91 9213932017 Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Eleven Mukhi (Om Harim Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>leven Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 12000.00
\n\n
Eleven Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 2500.00 </b>
E
    </string>
    <string name="bead_12">
        <b>
Rs. 18000.00(Twelve Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 3100.00(Twelve Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\
        Baarah (12) MukhiRudraksha (code:ARB12) Twelve Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be a form of the Sun. Lord Vishnu resides in it. If worn on right arm it removes all kinds of fears from the native. It protects from accidents. This gives magnetism to one who wears it regularly. This Rudraksha removes negative forces in the Aura and is a very effective remedy for mental problems. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Twelve Mukhi (Om Humm Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Twelve Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 18000.00
\n\n
Twelve Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 3100.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_13">
        <b>Rs. 21000.00 (Thirteen Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 4500.00 (Thirteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Terah(13) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB13) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Terah(13) Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Thirteen Mukhi Rudraksha is considered to be a form of Kamdeva. It improves ones attractiveness for the opposite sex. This is used for Vashikaran. A powerful Rudraksha for those who want to be the center of attraction for the opposite sex and also for people in public life. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Thirteen Mukhi (Om Shrom Namah)
\n\n

The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>Thirteen Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 21000.00
\n\n
Thirteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 4500.00 </b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_14">
        <b>
Rs. 120,000.00 (Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha)\nRs. 31000.00 (Fourteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha)</b>
        \n\n
        Choudah (14) Mukhi Rudraksha (code:ARB14) (FOR ANY QUERY ON Choudah (14) Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha gives strength and enthusiasm to one who wears it regularly. The lord of this Rudraksha is Hanumanji. Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha is said to do wonders in cases where one is unable to have children. In such cases both husband and wife should wear it. This gives the wearer fourteen kinds of knowledge and influence in all walks of life. Quality : Premium,
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
        \n\nFourteen Mukhi (Om Harim Namah)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Fourteen Mukhi Rudraksha Rs. 120,000.00
\n\n
Fourteen Mukhi Indonesian Rudraksha Rs. 31000.00</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_15">
<b>Fifteen Mukhi Rudraksha\n
Rs. 120,000.00</b>
        \n\n
        Fifteen Mukhi Rudraksha Product Code : ARB18 (FOR ANY QUERY ON Fifteen Mukhi Rudraksha, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Ruling planet is Saturn. Fifteen 15 Mukhi Rudraksha is held to sublimate the malefic effects of Saturn, Rahu and Ketu.It improving Intuitive, Abstract and Lateral thinking in addition the wearer finds high energy levels which fight aging and brings better performance in all fields of life. You need to call +91 9213932017
\n\n
Rudraksha means the tears of Lord Shiva. These tears came out of his eyes when he saw the sufferings of mankind. As per Shiv Mahapuran these mistical beads have supernatural powers. We procure these Rudrakshas from Jungles of Terai and Rameshwaram. 16 kinds of Rudraksha are available with us. From the very coveted One Mukhi to 15 Mukhi and even the Rare Gauri Shankar is available with us. All Rudrakshas are Abhimantrit by Shri Pankaj Khanna
\n\n
Fifteen faced Rudraksha is very powerful Rudraksha for those working accomplish Mukti freedom from bondage and Moksa that is Liberation in this physical lifetime. Pashu means individual soul or Jeeva , Pati means Lord and God and Master and Shiva all as one in the same. Pashupati is Lord of Individuals , Lord Siva Lord of animals.
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 120,000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_16">
<b>Sixteen Mukhi Rudraksha
\nRs. 150,000</b>
        \n\n
        Sixteen Mukhi Rudraksha is Mahamrityunjaya form of Lord Shiva. This rudraksha is form of Mahakal. The wearer becomes fearless and gets victory against the most fearsome of diseases and adverse circumstances. A home in which this Rudraksha is kept is free from thefts, fire and accidents. It protects from physical illness due to placement of planets. If one has fear of loss of a loved one or fear of loss of name and fame or loss of faith in oneself or fear of death, then one should wear the Mahamrityunjaya Rudraksha which is 16 mukhi. Mahakal is fearsome form of Lord Shiva which He assumed when Sati burned herself in fire. Even Yama the Lord of Death turns back from the wearer of this rudraksha. Price will be decided on demand
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n<b>
Rs. 150,000.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_17">
<b>Seventeen Mukhi Rudraksha
\nRs. 150000.00</b>
        \n\n
        Seventeen Mukhi Rudrasha face Mukhi. (FOR ANY QUERY ON Seventee Mukhi Rudrasha, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Seventeen Mukhi Rudraksha is form of Mata Katyani. Katyani Devi is sixth form of Goddess Durga. It removes obstacles in path and gives immense prosperity. The wearer gets fruits of Dharma, Artha, Kama and Moksha. Wearer lives with immense power and divine magnetism. Gets freedom from diseases, losses, sadness and fears. It gives fulfillment of all desires related to getting a life partner, progeny, good luck and prosperity Represents: Mata Katyani Mantra :- Beeja mantra: Om Kama Kam Katyayani Swaha Wearing mantra: Om Hreem Hoom Hoom Namah. Price will be decided on demand
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n
<b>Rs. 150000.00</b>

    </string>
    <string name="bead_18">
<b>EIGHTEEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>
        \n\n
        Eighteen Mukhi Rudraksha (FOR ANY QUERY ON Eighteen Mukhi Rudraksha, CALL 0091 - 9213932017) This rudraksha is form of Goddess earth. The wearer gets health, strength and intelligence. The wearer gets victory in whatever he does, gets immense power and fulfillment of desires. By blessings of Mother earth, the wearer always remains in abundance. It is ideal for people in real-estate and land dealings. If worn by ladies who are prone to abortion, it protects the unborn child and she is able to give birth to a healthy beautiful baby. Represents: Goddess Earth Mantra :- Beeja mantra: Om Hreem Shreem Vasudhaye Swaha Om Hreem Hoom Ektatva rupe Hoom Hreem om\r\nPrice will be decided on demand
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_19">
<b>NINETEEN MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>\n\n
        Nineteen Mukhi Rudraksha , (FOR ANY QUERY ON Nineteen Mukhi Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) is form of Lord Narayan the supreme of all Gods. The wearer never has lack of anything in life. It gives immense wealth, success in business , abundance in all spheres and good health . The wearer gets blessings of Vishnu and Goddess Laxmi and is blessed with many virtues , beauty and prosperity. The wearer gets freedom from dreaded diseases , gets perfect life partner . Nineteen Mukhi Rudraksha removes obstacles in job/business/education and removes planetary afflictions. The wearer gets Moksha. It Represents: Lord Narayana and Goddess Laxmi Mantra :- Beeja mantra: Om Vam Vishnave Sheershayane Swaha Wearing mantra: Om Hreem Hoom Namah
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.

    </string>
    <string name="bead_20">
<b>TWENTY MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>\n\n
        Twenty Mukhi Rudraksha This Rudraksha is Brahma swarupa. It has energies of the nine planets, Eight Dikpals (Indra, Varun, Yama, Kuber, Agni, Vayu, Niriti and Ishan) and Tridevas (Brahma , Vishnu , Mahesh). This is highly rare Rudraksha and due to its energies the wearer gets power to achieve almost anything he desires. Twenty Mukhi Rudraksha Represents: Brahma Swarupa Mantra: Beeja mantra: Rudrarupaye Kalpante Namastubhyam Trimurtaye Wearing mantra: Brahmatave Srajaye vishvam Sthitow Palyate punah. Price will be decided on demand
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_21">
    <b>TWENTY ONE MUKHI RUDRAKSHA</b>\n\n
        Twenty One Mukhi Rudrkahsa. A Rudraksha of Twenty-one face is Lord Shiva. By wearing this remission from the sins of bramahatya could be procured. Moreover wearing it or worshiping it in the house, stabilizes the entire environment and relationship of human to soul. The man hold this Rudraksha is never down on his achievement. All Gods reside within the surrounding of this Rudraksha where it is placed for worship. Wealth and health always remains within the family possesing this rudraksha.The bearer will famous for prosperity and spirituality and always remains in the path of Sanatan Dharma.It is helpful in opening the third eye chakra which governs clairvoyance, sharpened skills, heightened state of awareness etc. Prices will be decided on demand
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_trijuti">
<b>Trijuti Rudraksha</b>\n\n
        Trijuti Rudraksha Code : Trijuti Rudraksha is Trijuti i.e., Bramha,Vishnu and Shiva Roopam. Those who hold or worship this great Rudraksha gets Bramha Gyan.The bearer enjoys superpower in the society. All the benefit of diffrent Mukhi of Rudraksha will be fulfilled by possesing it. Diseases of all sorts in the body internally as well as externally never touches him.
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
    </string>
    <string name="bead_ganesh">
<b>
    GANESH RUDRAKSHA
\nRs. 900.00
</b>\n\n
        Ganesh Rudraksha Code : ARB16 (FOR ANY QUERY ON Ganesh Rudraksha CALL 0091 - 9213932017) Ganesha Rudraksha represents Lord Ganesha
        \n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
\n\n
<b>Rs. 900.00 </b>
    </string>
    <string name="bead_gauri">
        <b>Gauri Shankar Rudraksha\n
Rs. 12000.00 </b>\n\n
        Guari Shankar Rudraksha is a Rudraksha that looks as if two rudraksha are joined together one smaller than the other. This is said to fulfill all desires are makes the person satisfied and contented in life. Especially used by people in business who want to earn money in big way and earn it fast.
\n\n
Mantra for Gauri Shankar Rudraksha
\n
Gauri Shankar Rudraksha      (Om Namah Shivai)
\n\n
The Mantra has to be recited on a Rudhraksha mala and should be spoken in such a way that at least you can hear it. Shri Shiv Mahapuran is of the view that Rudhraksha does not give its full results without the use of proper mantras.
<b>\nRs. 12000.00 </b>
    </string>


</resources>
